So, today I want to take my time and
take
our time to teach and I'm going to
base
100% of my teaching on a book that I
wrote called Understanding Generational
Family Battles.
And there is a small heading there
called Redeeming Your Bloodline.
And what I decided today is that
this book will be available and I'm
going to give it at an offer today.
I'm I'm going to give it at 500 only.
And the reason why I'm doing that is
because I will not be able to capture
everything that I have written in this
book. Are we together?
Are we together?
Are there people who come to my office
and they tell me, "Pastor, I'm going
through a family issue." And what I do
always give them this book. The second
thing that we are going to do,
we will also go to our Life Church page
and locate some teachings that I did on
the same matter and we are going to
consolidate them and share them and
re-share them again on our our WhatsApp
platforms and even on our our online
platforms because
I believe that God is interested in the
deliverance of men, especially from
their families.
There are many things that we choose in
life, but we never choose our families.
That automatically tells you
that if I have no power over my family,
then whatever I find in that family can
either shape my life or I can rise above
it if it is negative and begin to deal
with it and fight with it and pursue
another path of life. So, that is the
sad reality about family. We don't
choose our families. Um there is no
place where people applied and say that
I want to be born and come from a
certain family. And the second thing is
that
every family, and I won't lie to you,
whether rich or poor,
it is not about the economic advantage
of a family.
Every family has something that they are
dealing with.
Even where I come from, there are things
I am believing God as an individual that
they are going to end with me and they
will never and they will not advance in
the next generation. And so, it is very
important to understand we never chose
our families. It is also important to
understand that every family has a
something that people are dealing with.
You could be looking at somebody and
think they are okay, but I want to
assure you we are all fighting different
battles in different families. And
today, by this revelation, I want to
believe there will be an additional
wisdom and an additional tool for you to
live a victorious life and for you to
redeem your bloodline by the ordinances
of Elohim.
There are four things that we are going
to look at. And this is what I call the
four common battles in families.
THE FOUR COMMON battles in families.
Number one,
WE HAVE WHAT WE call generational
altars.
Generational altars.
And let me be very categorical.
Uh we MUST TEACH THIS MATTER with a lot
of balance.
Because when you are born again,
there are certain realities under the
new creation reality and this reality
gives you an exclusion
TOWARDS SOME CERTAIN MATTERS in your
family.
BUT WHEN I LOOK AT THE WORD SALVATION,
THE NAME SALVATION COMES FROM A GREEK
word soteria.
That is the NAME SALVATION. IT COMES
FROM A GREEK WORD SOTERIA.
And in that GREEK WORD SOTERIA,
THAT NAME HAS ALMOST
FIVE TO SEVEN MEANINGS.
IT HAS ALMOST FIVE TO SEVEN MEANINGS.
SO, when we talk of salvation, MANY OF
THE people always think salvation is the
altar call.
THE THE THE THE THE ALTAR CALL WHEN
PEOPLE COME TO THE ALTAR,
THAT IS THE BEGINNING OF A JOURNEY
CALLED
OF SALVATION.
SO, THAT IS THAT THAT THAT THAT MOMENT,
THE grace and the life of God is
released SO THAT NOW YOU begin a journey
and the journey is called the journey of
salvation. Are we together up to there?
And so, IN SALVATION,
THERE IS THE WORD HEALING.
In the name soteria, THERE IS ALSO THE
WORD DELIVERANCE.
THERE IS also the word deliverance.
And when we begin to deal with matters,
FAMILY, WE ARE NOW DEALING WITH A
DIMENSION OF SALVATION which is
deliverance.
[Music]
So, SALVATION COMES AS A PACKAGE.
THERE IS THE REALITY OF WHO YOU BECAME
IN CHRIST.
BUT AS YOU PURSUE THAT REALITY, there is
THERE ARE CERTAIN THINGS THAT BEGIN to
leave your life and THERE ARE CERTAIN
SHACKLES, THERE ARE CERTAIN CHAINS,
THERE ARE CERTAIN CONNECTIONS, THERE ARE
CERTAIN patterns that begin to lose your
life.
So, it is POSSIBLE FOR A MAN TO BE BORN
AGAIN
AND TO LIVE A VICTORIOUS LIFE.
AND THAT VICTORIOUS LIFE, IT IS NOT AN
instant event. THAT IS WHY WE TEACH THE
WORD OF GOD. EVERY LIGHT THAT COMES TO
YOUR LIFE IS AN ADVANTAGE AND IS A
BUILDING block towards living a
victorious life.
The second thing, TODAY WE ARE ALSO
DEALING WITH A REALITY THAT JOSHUA
DECLARED WHEN THE WHOLE OF ISRAEL
BACKSLID.
JOSHUA CAME AND SAID, "AS FOR ME AND MY
HOUSE,
WE SHALL SERVE THE LORD."
SO, I AM ALSO INTENTIONAL
to make SURE THAT YOU DON'T ENJOY
SALVATION ALONE.
THAT SOMEBODY WILL GET MAD IN THE SPIRIT
AND SOMEBODY WILL GO BACK TO HIS
FATHER'S house and begin to deal with
things that have bound that family.
OBADIAH CHAPTER NUMBER ONE AND VERSE 20
and 21, it says, "And saviors shall
arise from Zion." So, there are people
here BY THE GRACE OF GOD AND WE
CELEBRATE YOU. YOU ARE A living reality
of the NEW CREATION REALITY. NO CURSES
OVER YOUR LIFE, NO ALTAR SPEAKING OVER
YOUR LIFE, NOTHING IN YOUR BLOODLINE IS
AFFECTING YOU. BUT NOW YOU MUST ARISE
BECAUSE THERE ARE AUNTIES and uncles,
THERE ARE BROTHERS AND SISTERS THAT NEED
THE VERY victory that you have in your
life.
SO, WE DIDN'T GET BORN AGAIN FOR
OURSELVES. WE ARE going to demand for
the release of our families.
BUT THERE ARE ALSO PEOPLE HERE
THAT BY THIS REVELATION, THEY WILL SEE
AND UNDERSTAND SOME THINGS AND THEY WILL
NOW HAVE ACCURACY OF THE BATTLES they
need to engage in and what they need to
destroy and what they need to expect out
of this revelation. Are we together?
Are we together up to there?
SO, THE FIRST THING I WANT TO look at is
generational altars.
GENERATIONAL ALTARS. WHY AM I CALLING IT
A GENERATIONAL ALTAR?
BECAUSE
THIS IS AN ALTAR
THAT ALTERS THE LIVES OF MEN in a
generation.
IT IS AN ALTAR THAT ALTERS THE LIVES OF
MEN IN A GENERATION.
THERE ARE TWO TYPES OF ALTARS OR LET ME
DEFINE AN ALTAR. WHAT IS AN ALTAR?
AN ALTAR is an exalted monument.
AN ALTAR IS AN EXALTED MONUMENT
THAT CONNECTS THE PHYSICAL REALM to the
SPIRITUAL REALM.
AN ALTAR
IS AN EXALTED MONUMENT
THAT connects
the spiritual realm, the physical realm
to the spiritual realm.
AN ALTAR IS NOT A FLAT MONUMENT. IT MUST
be exalted
because it has to affect the physical
realm, SO IT CANNOT be in the level of
the PHYSICAL REALM. IT MUST BE EXALTED
ABOVE THE PHYSICAL REALM.
SO, AN ALTAR IS AN EXALTED MONUMENT THAT
AFFECTS THE PHYSICAL THAT CONNECTS THE
PHYSICAL REALM with the spiritual realm.
AN ALTAR IS A PATHWAY.
IS A PATHWAY OF TRANSACTION between the
spiritual and the physical. An altar IS
A PATHWAY. SOME PEOPLE CALL IT A PORTAL.
AN ALTAR IS A PATHWAY OF TRANSACTION
BETWEEN the physical and the spiritual.
AN ALTAR IS A KEY THAT OPENS THE
SPIRITUAL. AN ALTAR IS A KEY THAT OPENS
THE SPIRITUAL REALM. AN ALTAR IS A KEY
THAT OPENS THE spiritual realm.
THE PROTOCOLS OF AN ALTAR, THERE ARE
THREE THINGS FOR AN ALTAR TO BE
FUNCTIONAL.
THERE ARE MUST BE A PRIEST. THERE ARE
MUST BE AN ALTAR AND THERE MUST BE A
SACRIFICE.
FOR AN ALTAR TO BE FUNCTIONAL, THESE
THREE things must BE THERE. NUMBER ONE,
A PRIEST. Civilians don't ATTEND TO
ALTARS.
ALTARS ANSWER TO PRIEST. SO, THERE ARE
MUST BE A PRIEST, THERE ARE MUST BE AN
ALTAR, AN EXALTED MONUMENT, AND THERE
ARE MUST BE A SACRIFICE.
AN ALTAR WITHOUT A SACRIFICE IS A
MONUMENT THAT CANNOT
invoke any transaction.
AND SO, AN ALTAR WITHOUT A PRIEST, IT
CANNOT HAVE ANY ADDRESS. SO, THERE ARE
MUST BE A PRIEST, THERE ARE MUST BE AN
ALTAR, AND THERE MUST BE A SACRIFICE.
ARE WE TOGETHER up to there?
In the IN THE REALMS OF ALTARS, YOU CAN
HAVE A LIVING ALTAR AND
AN ABANDONED OR
AN ABANDONED ALTAR. THERE ARE TWO OF
THEM. YOU CAN HAVE A LIVING ALTAR OR AN
ABANDONED ALTAR.
WHAT IS A LIVING ALTAR?
A living altar IS AN ALTAR THAT HAS A
FUNCTIONAL PRIEST THAT PERPETUALLY AND
CONTINUALLY sacrifices on the altar.
So, a living altar is an altar THAT HAS
A FUNCTIONAL PRIEST AND IT has
functional sacrifices.
A LIVING ALTAR IS AN ALTAR THAT HAS A
FUNCTIONAL PRIEST AND IT ALSO HAS A
FUNCTIONAL SACRIFICE.
WE ALSO HAVE AN ABANDONED ALTAR.
MEANING THAT SOMEONE EXALTED AN ALTAR.
THE ALTAR DID ITS ASSIGNMENT, BUT THAT
ALTAR DOES NOT HAVE A PRIEST, neither
does it have a sacrifice.
BUT, YOU CANNOT IGNORE THAT THE ALTAR is
still there.
BECAUSE AN ALTAR IS A KEY IN THE
SPIRITUAL. SO, SOMEONE WENT AND DID
BUSINESS WITH THAT ALTAR. MAYBE THE MAN
DIED. BUT, THE OPERATIONS OF THAT ALTAR
CAN still be felt in that family.
Let me give AN EXAMPLE.
A MAN WANTED TO BE WEALTHY.
AND THE MAN WENT TO A WITCH.
AND WHEN HE WENT TO A WITCH, THAT WITCH
IS A PRIEST.
WHEN HE WENT TO A WITCH, THERE WAS A
DEMAND OF A CERTAIN SACRIFICE. SO, WHEN
THE MAN DELIVERED THE SACRIFICE,
WHAT HAPPENED IS THAT THAT SACRIFICE
OPENED THE HEAVENS
OF THE SPIRITUAL REALM AND CERTAIN
SPIRITS WERE RELEASED TO SPONSOR,
SUPPORT, AND FACILITATE THE MAN IN HIS
WEALTH CREATION.
SO, THAT MAN COULD BE MY FATHER. SO, AS
LONG AS THE MAN WAS ALIVE, HE
went to a witch. EVERY TIME HE WOULD GO
TO THE VILLAGE WITH A SACRIFICE,
SERVE THE ALTAR, AND THE MAN BUSINESS
GREW, AND HIS BUSINESS EXPANDED, BUT HE
DID business by the system OF AN ALTAR.
NOW, MY FATHER IS DEAD. THAT MAN IS
DEAD. BUT, THE REALITY OF THAT ALTAR IS
NOT DEAD.
The spirits THAT HE INVOKED SO THAT NOW
THE BUSINESS could prosper, the spirits
ARE NOT DEAD. SO, I HAVE INHERITED THE
BUSINESS FROM MY FATHER.
BUT, WHAT I DON'T KNOW, MY FATHER WAS
NOT JUST SELLING PRODUCTS. MY FATHER WAS
DOING BUSINESS WITH AN ALTAR AND A
SACRIFICE AND A PRIESTHOOD. SO, THE
PRIESTHOOD IS ABANDONED, THE ALTAR IS
ABANDONED, NO SACRIFICE, AND I BEGIN TO
FACE FRUSTRATION IN THIS BUSINESS. I
CANNOT FIX THE BUSINESS BY STUDYING
ECONOMICS.
BECAUSE THE BACKGROUND OF THIS BUSINESS
IS AN ALTAR. SO, THE BUSINESS CAN GO
DOWN. ANYTHING I TRY TO DO in the name
OF BUSINESS MAY NOT PROSPER BECAUSE
THERE IS A DEMONIC LEGALITY IN THE
SPIRIT THAT WE ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR MEN
TO PROSPER IN THIS HOME. SO, UNLESS YOU
GO TO THE ABANDONED ALTAR, NOBODY CAN
MOVE in business. Is someone GETTING ME?
SO, NOW THERE IS A DEMAND DEMONICALLY
BECAUSE A MAN OPENED A DOOR IN THE
SPIRIT, BUT THE MAN IS NOT THERE. SO,
YOU ARE DEALING WITH AN ABANDONED ALTAR.
BUT, THAT ALTAR IS STILL SPEAKING AND
CAUSING HAVOC IN THE FAMILY.
THAT'S AN ABANDONED ALTAR.
AND SOMETIMES,
IT IS EASY TO DEAL WITH AN ABANDONED
ALTAR BECAUSE BY THE REVELATION OF
CALVARY AND BY THE REVELATION OF THE
WORD OF GOD AND BY THE REVELATION OF THE
BLOOD OF YESHUA AND BY THE REVELATION OF
WHO YOU ARE IN CHRIST, YOU CAN DESTROY
THE OPERATION OF AN ALTAR. BUT, WHEN YOU
ARE DEALING WITH A LIVING ALTAR, YOU
MUST ALSO HAVE LIVING LIFESTYLE OF
CONSECRATION AND PRAYER.
THAT'S WHY SOME PEOPLE WILL RECEIVE
THEIR DELIVERANCE. THE LORD MIGHT TELL
YOU, "GO AND PRAY FOR A CERTAIN NUMBER
OF DAYS OR RELEASE A SACRIFICE." THE
INSTRUCTIONS VARY ACCORDING TO YOUR
LEVEL AND ACCORDING TO YOUR relationship
with God.
I was LISTENING TO A MAN OF GOD AND HE
SAID HE ENTERED INTO PRAYER FOR ALMOST
120 DAYS AND ON THE 120TH
DAY, HE SAW A MAN
MAN IN THE SPIRIT AND HE WAS holding
some goods. And he was told, "Go and
collect YOUR STUFF."
AND THEN HE SAW SOME THINGS WRITTEN THE
NAMES OF PEOPLE IN HIS FAMILY AND HE WAS
TOLD, "LEAVE THEM, COLLECT yours and go
because it will take certain labors in
the spirit for men to collect what IS
THEIRS." LATER, HE DISCOVERED THERE WAS
AN ANCIENT DEMONIC ALTAR THAT HAD TIED
THE WEALTH OF THEIR FAMILY. SO, THE
SOURCE OF THEIR POVERTY HAD NOTHING TO
DO WITH LAZINESS. THERE WAS AN ANCIENT
ENTITY THAT WAS DEMANDING REVERENCE,
DEMANDING WORSHIP, DEMANDING SACRIFICE
SO THAT THE FAMILY CAN PROSPER.
And it was after engagement in prayer
that that THING HAPPENED. A FRIEND OF
MINE WAS LANGUISHING. MINISTRY WAS NOT
WORKING. NOTHING WAS WORKING. HE LIVES
IN JORO. HE ENTERED INTO A 40-DAY
PRAYER. ON THE 40TH DAY, HE SAW AN ELDER
SITTING ON A THREE-LEGGED CHAIR AND HE
asked him, "WHAT IS YOUR PROBLEM?" AND
THEN THE ELDER RELEASED A PAPER. AND
WHEN HE RELEASED THAT PAPER, THE
FOLLOWING DAY, THE MAN WENT AND SAW A
TITLE DEED. IT WAS STILL IN THEIR HOME.
HE SAW A TITLE DEED OF 50 ACRES THAT WAS
LOST AND THAT TITLE DEED, THE LAND WAS
PRIME AND THAT LAND COULD NOT BE LOCATED
AND THAT'S HOW THEIR POVERTY ENDED.
THERE ARE CERTAIN SPIRITUAL OPERATIONS
that are needed for certain things to
give way. And I pray by the END OF THIS
SERVICE, THERE WILL BE GRACE OVER YOUR
LIFE. THERE ARE THINGS THAT MUST LOCATE
YOU. THERE ARE THINGS THERE ARE CERTAIN
SPIRITUAL OPERATIONS THAT WE MUST ENTER
INTO SO THAT THE CYCLE can come to an
end.
So, you can either deal with a living
altar
or a dead or an abandoned altar.
THEM THAT ARE DEALING WITH LIVING
ALTARS, WE HAVE AUNTIES, we have
sisters, WE HAVE PARENTS WHO THEIR
SYSTEM IS WITCHCRAFT. THAT'S A LIVING
ALTAR.
SUCH A MAN, YOU CANNOT AFFORD TO SLEEP
IN PRAYER.
BY DEFAULT, YOUR LIFE IS DIFFERENT FROM
PEOPLE WHO COME FROM A FAMILY WHERE
EVERYONE IS BORN AGAIN AND THEY HAVE
DEALT WITH SOME POWERS.
THAT'S WHY OUR PRAYER LIFE CANNOT BE THE
SAME.
NO, NO.
SOME SOME PEOPLE WILL PERPETUALLY BE ON
A FASTING SCHEDULE BECAUSE THEY ARE
DEALING WITH SOMETHING THAT IS ALIVE.
SOME PEOPLE WILL PERPETUALLY BE SLEEPING
and nothing is happening. Please tell
your neighbor, "Neighbor,
we could be deskmates, but we are not
WARFARE MATES. EVERY PATH IS UNIQUE.
Are we together?"
And now, IN THE SAME LANGUAGE OF ALTARS,
THERE IS NO ALTAR WITHOUT A GOD.
SO, WHEN YOU BEGIN TO INTERROGATE WHAT
WE call generational altars, you will
also come to what we call household
gods.
Household gods.
In the book of Genesis, CHAPTER NUMBER
31 AND VERSE 19,
WE SEE THAT RACHEL STOLE THE GODS OF HER
FATHER LABAN.
THESE are household gods.
Household gods.
[Music]
May the Holy Ghost give me strength
today.
Genesis, chapter number So, IT WAS WHEN
HIS MASTER HAD THE WORD, which his wife
spoke to him saying, "Your did to me
after this manner." No, okay. I can SEE
HE'S THERE. NOW LABAN HAD GONE TO SHEAR
HIS SHEEP, AND RACHEL HAD STOLEN THEIR
HOUSEHOLD IDOLS
THAT WERE HER FATHER'S.
LABAN WAS A DIVINER.
A DIVINER IS A COUSIN OF A WITCH.
THEY ARE RELATED IN OPERATIONS.
LABAN CAME AND TOLD JACOB, "I HAVE
LEARNED BY DIVINATION
THAT IN YOUR LIFE THERE IS A GRACE,
AND I PROSPER
BECAUSE OF THE GRACE THAT YOU CARRY."
SO THE MAN LOCATED JACOB IN THE SPIRIT.
ALLOW ME TO SAY THIS. THERE IS A LEVEL
OF PROSPERITY WHICH IS NOT A PRODUCT OF
HARD WORK, BUT IT IS A PRODUCT OF
ANOINTING AND GRACE IN THE SPIRIT.
AND MEN CAN BE LOCATED. THE WISE MEN OF
BABYLON LOCATED JESUS AS A STAR.
AND THEY INTERPRETED IT CORRECTLY.
AND SO LABAN LOCATED JACOB. REMEMBER
JACOB WAS CARRYING A TETRA PIPE
ANOINTING.
WHAT WAS IN ABRAHAM, WHAT WAS IN ISAAC
WAS NOW UPON HIM.
WHATEVER ABRAHAM CAN
THIS ANOINTING LANDED ON ONE MAN.
BY THE TIME HE'S GETTING IN THE HOUSE OF
JACOB, WHATEVER HE TOUCHES HAS TO
PROSPER. AND JACOB BY DIVINATION LOCATES
THE MAN AND REALIZES, "THIS IS NOT AN
ORDINARY EMPLOYEE. THIS ONE IS A CARRIER
OF A GRACE. IF ONLY I CAN ATTACH MY LIFE
TO HIM, I WILL PROSPER."
Can I surprise you?
Do you KNOW THERE ARE CERTAIN RELIGIONS
WHERE MEN DON'T MARRY FOR LOVE? They
marry for grace.
THERE ARE CERTAIN RELIGIONS WHERE PEOPLE
ARE CONNECTED TO A MAN.
PEOPLE ARE CONNECTED TO A MAN NOT
BECAUSE OF THE LOVE THE MAN HAS FOR THE
WOMAN, IT'S BECAUSE OF THE GRACE THE MAN
CARRIES.
SO THE MOTHER WILL FACILITATE THAT MY
DAUGHTER IS MARRIED TO A CERTAIN MAN, OR
A MAN WILL BE FORCED TO MARRY A CERTAIN
WOMAN SO THAT HIS BUSINESSES CAN
PROSPER.
LET ME EVEN GO FURTHER. THERE ARE PEOPLE
WHO EMPLOY YOU NOT BECAUSE of your
papers.
THEY MUST SCAN YOU IN the spirit and
locate who YOU ARE IN THE SPIRIT. THE
ERROR IS WHEN OH MY GOD. WHEN THE
KINGDOM OF DARKNESS KNOWS YOU, BUT YOU
DON'T KNOW WHO YOU ARE.
IT MEANS A MAN CAN KEEP YOU IN A JOB NOT
BECAUSE YOU ARE A HARD WORKER, IT'S
BECAUSE THE MAN KNOWS AS LABAN KNEW, "AS
LONG AS JACOB IS IN THE HOUSE, I WILL
PROSPER." MAY THE LORD REVEAL TO YOU
WHAT YOU CARRY.
NOBODY WILL PLUG THEIR SYSTEM INTO YOUR
SYSTEM. MAY THE LORD REVEAL YOUR
IDENTITY IN THE SPIRIT. SOME OF YOU THE
GRACE YOU CARRY IS THE GRACE OF WEALTH.
SOME OF YOU THE GRACE YOU CARRY IS THE
GRACE TO PROSPER.
[Music]
THERE ARE PEOPLE you marry them and you
prosper.
[Music]
NOT BECAUSE THEY ARE DOING ANYTHING IN
YOUR LIFE, BECAUSE OF THAT CONNECTION.
HI.
I feel like I want TO DWELL THERE.
BECAUSE THERE IS AN IGNORANCE IN THE
HOUSE OF GOD. YET MEN IN THE MARKETPLACE
DON'T DO BUSINESS WITH CVs only.
MEN DO BUSINESS WITH THEIR ALTARS FIRST.
SO A MAN MUST LOCATE YOU IN THE SPIRIT,
AND THE NEXT THING YOU'LL BEGIN TO HEAR,
"THIS IS THE PERSON WE WANT." AND THEN
YOU COME TO CHURCH AND SAY, "You know,
GOD HAS GIVEN me favor with this
community." Before you begin to give
THAT TESTIMONY, ASK YOURSELF, "WHY DID
THIS community first of ALL LOVE ME? WHY
IS IT THAT THEY ARE ENTRUSTING ME WITH
SOME OF THEIR PRIVATE MATTERS? WHO AM I
IN THE SPIRIT?"
BEFORE YOU REALIZE YOU ARE meant to be A
BILLIONAIRE, BUT SOMEONE HAS CONNECTED
their system to your system. In the
realm OF THE SPIRIT, DESTINIES CAN BE
HIJACKED.
AND IT IS SO BAD THAT EVEN IN THE
CHRISTENDOM,
IN CHRISTIANITY, there are people who
can locate you as A PREACHER, BUT THE
NEXT THING THEY ARE NOT INVITING you to
preach, THEY ARE INVITING YOU SO THAT
THEY CAN HACK YOUR SYSTEM. SOMEONE CAN
INVITE YOU AS A WORSHIPER NOT BECAUSE
THEY LOVE YOUR SONGS, THEY WANT TO HACK
YOUR SYSTEM.
That's why I tell my sons here,
sometimes I see them on pedestals and I
cover them.
BECAUSE THERE ARE CERTAIN ALTARS. MEN
WILL GIVE YOU MONEY,
BUT THEY KNOW WHAT YOU CARRY. SO THEY
WANT TO THEY MIGHT SAY, "OH, YOU KNOW,
THERE'S A GRACE YOU CARRY." YES, WE KNOW
THERE'S A GRACE WE CARRY, BUT NOT
EVERYONE HONORS THE GRACE WE CARRY. SOME
ARE THERE TO MANIPULATE AND TAKE
ADVANTAGE OF THAT GRACE. THAT'S WHY
NEVER GO WHERE YOU'RE INVITED, GO WHERE
GOD HAS SENT YOU. NOT EVERY INVITATION
IS YOUR INVITATION. NOT EVERY PROMOTION
IS YOUR PROMOTION. NOT EVERY DOOR IS
YOUR OPEN DOOR. HEAR GOD WELL, and know
this is the will of God.
That's why when we are attacked with
carnality, we cannot audit what God
wants.
We celebrate every open door where our
men are serious with their stuff.
I know a woman of God from this nation
WHO USED TO OPERATE IN THE MIRACULOUS.
THE FATHERS WILL TELL US THE STORY, AND
THEY WILL TELL US, "THIS WOMAN OF GOD,
her system was hijacked by a Nigerian
father."
[Music]
SO THE MIRACULOUS SHIFTED FROM HER TO
THE MAN.
I'm talking about church.
BECAUSE SPIRITUALITY CARRIES SOME
CERTAIN PATTERNS. The demonic CAN USE
IT, AND strange men in church can also
use it.
That's why you must BE ALERT.
NOT EVERY MAN
THAT INVITES YOU ON A TABLE IS honoring
you.
Some are there to hijack, to connect
their demonic pipes into your system. SO
YOU LABOR IN PRAYER, BUT SOMEONE IS
DRAWING.
SOMEONE KNOWS YOU CARRY A GENUINE GRACE
FOR WEALTH. YOU HAVE NOT YET MANIFESTED,
AND NOW THEY HAVE PLANTED you in that
business. Because they know AS LONG AS
JACOB IS IN THE HOUSE, Laban will
prosper. SO NOW YOU UNDERSTAND WHY LABAN
HAD TO SHORT-CHANGE HIM. That instead of
7 years, the man has to work for 14
YEARS.
THE MAN LABORED AND MADE Jacob wealthy.
That man, his presence was the reason
for his wealth. And then you BEGIN TO
REALIZE THAT LABAN had some household
gods.
HE HAD GODS IN HIS OWN HOUSE. YOU CANNOT
HAVE A GOD WITHOUT AN ALTAR. SO THE MAN
WAS A PRIEST OF A CERTAIN ORDER IN THE
REALMS of the spirit. Be afraid of these
communities that don't hide their idols.
Be afraid of them.
Yeah, someone will put an idol on the
shop,
and they venerate them. THEY THEY ARE
NOT AFRAID. THEY WILL BURN INCENSE IN
YOUR PRESENCE.
Because they are not afraid. THEY KNOW
WHAT THEIR IDOLS DOES,
BUT YOU CANNOT PRAY in tongues IN THEIR
PRESENCE.
YET A MAN CAN BURN INCENSE IN YOUR
PRESENCE. NO, THERE ARE TIMES YOU ALSO
NEED TO DRAW THE LINE. AS THEY BURN
THEIR INCENSE, YOU BURN IN THE HOLY
GHOST. YOU HAVE TO COUNTER SOME
ATMOSPHERES.
Am I speaking to anyone?
Yeah.
Because we live in an age where men are
not afraid. They are now exalting idols
all over. So and anywhere there is a
household god, there must be a altar in
that house.
SO IF A MAN GOES TO A WITCH, HE'S
INTRODUCING the idols of that witch in
the home.
NOW WE WE ARE IN A GENERATION. HI.
IT TAKES BOLDNESS TO SAY THIS.
WE ARE IN A GENERATION WHERE MEN ARE
GOING BACK TO THEIR TRADITIONAL ALTARS.
YOU CANNOT SERVE THAT ALTAR AND SERVE
YAHWEH. You must choose one.
IN THE NAME OF TRADITION, THERE IS AN
ELDERSHIP RISING INITIATING YOUNG MEN
AND introducing them as priests to a
certain order. Allow me to tell you the
truth. FROM THE DAY THE BIBLE WAS
WRITTEN, ONLY ONE ALTAR RULED ISRAEL.
THE DAY THEY WENT TO BAAL AND ASHERAH,
Jehovah left town.
COMING TO CHURCH DOES NOT DELIVER YOU,
WHEREAS YOU HAVE SOME THINGS YOU GOT
FROM your village, and yet you keep them
dearly. YOU MUST CHOOSE YE which God you
want to serve. IF IT IS THE GOD OF YOUR
FATHERS, PLEASE LEAVE CHURCH.
VENERATE THEM. SACRIFICE TO THEM.
WORSHIP THEM. HOLY, IF YOU ARE SERVING
THE LORD, TAKE AWAY THE IDOLS OUT OF
YOUR CAMP. THE BIBLE SAYS THEY LOST IN
THEIR BATTLE WHEN THEY WERE GOING TO
TAKE OVER THE CITY OF AI. THEY LOST IN A
BATTLE, AND JOSHUA WENT IN ON ONE DAY
FAST AND BEGAN TO ASK THE LORD, "WHAT IS
THE PROBLEM?" THE LORD SAID, "There are
things hidden in the CAMP OF ACHAN.
THERE ARE THINGS IN THAT CAMP. THE
REASON WHY I CANNOT MOVE IN VICTORY. MEN
HAVE STRANGE THINGS IN THEIR HOUSES. LET
THEM OFFLOAD THEM, AND JEHOVAH will come
back to town. Offload the idols. I SAY
OFFLOAD THE IDOLS. I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOUR GRANDMOTHER GAVE YOU. A CHAIN
TELLING YOU IT'S FOR PROTECTION. WE ARE
NOT PROTECTED BY BEADS. WE ARE PROTECTED
BY THE BLOOD OF YESHUA. WE ARE NOT
PROTECTED BY WATER. WE ARE NOT PROTECTED
BY WHAT THEY GAVE YOU AS SOMETHING TO
BATHE WITH, AS SOMETHING TO PUT IN YOUR
FOOD, A CERTAIN POWDER WRAPPED UP IN
BANANA LEAVES. IF THAT IS YOUR
PROTECTION,
LEAVE JESUS.
HALLELUJAH.
WE HAVE TO BE RADICAL.
BECAUSE THE DAYS WE ARE LIVING, IT IS
EITHER JEHOVAH OR JEHOVAH.
TELL YOUR NEIGHBOR, "NEIGHBOR,
WE CANNOT MIX THIS MATTER. IT IS EITHER
ELOHIM OR ELOHIM.
IF YOU NEED VICTORY, YOU MUST BE
SUBMISSIVE TO ONE ALTAR. HALLELUJAH.
AND HERE IS A MAN NOW, JACOB IS LOCATED
BY THE SYSTEM of divination. And so
THERE IS A HOUSEHOLD GOD. LOOK AT THE
BOOK OF JUDGES CHAPTER NUMBER SIX FROM
VERSE 25. WHERE THERE IS A HOUSEHOLD
GOD, THERE MUST BE a household altar.
This is the life This is the life of
Gideon.
Judges chapter number six from verse 25.
Judges six from verse 25. Judges six
from verse 25. I believe light is coming
on your way.
Hallelujah.
I believe DELIVERANCE IS COMING. NOW, IT
CAME TO PASS THE SAME NIGHT THAT THE
LORD said to him, "Take your father's
young bull, the second bull of seven
years old, and tear down the altar of
BAAL THAT YOUR FATHER HAS, AND CUT DOWN
THE WOODEN image that is beside it." On
Sunday I taught about the law of
planting AND UPROOTING. SO THIS is
Gideon. He must FIRST BRING DOWN THE
ALTAR IN HIS FATHER'S HOUSE AND THE
ALTAR THAT COMMANDS THE TERRITORY. So
that he CAN NOW BRING UP A GODLY ALTAR.
SOME OF YOU THE GIDEON ANOINTING IS
ABOUT to land over you. BECAUSE THERE
ARE CERTAIN OPERATIONS IN YOUR FATHER'S
HOUSE, NOBODY HAS EVER ATTEMPTED THEM.
BUT THE POWER OF THE HOLY GHOST, THE
SAME SPIRIT THAT CAME UPON PETER ON THE
DAY OF PENTECOST, AND HE BROKE THE DOORS
BECAUSE HE WAS AFRAID OF THE MEN, THAT
SPIRIT OF BOLDNESS IS COMING UPON YOU.
THIS DECEMBER, YOU ARE NOT GOING FOR
CELEBRATION, YOU ARE GOING FOR AN
OPERATION. THE LORD WILL BEGIN TO OPEN
YOUR EYES. HE WILL SHOW YOU THIS IS NOT
A TREE, UNDER THIS TREE, THERE ARE
CERTAIN THINGS THAT WERE BURIED. THIS IS
NOT JUST A HOUSE, UNDER THIS ROOM, THERE
ARE CERTAIN RITUALS THAT WERE PERFORMED.
YOU WILL ENTER THERE WITH THE POWER OF
THE HOLY GHOST AS A PRIEST OF ANOTHER
ORDER, READY TO BRING DOWN THE ALTARS
AND THE GODS IN YOUR FATHER'S HOUSE.
IT TAKES A MAN of boldness.
The Bible says, "NOW IT CAME TO PASS THE
SAME NIGHT THAT THE LORD SAID TO HIM,
"TAKE YOUR FATHER'S YOUNG BULL, THE
SECOND BULL of seven years old, and tear
down the ALTAR OF BAAL THAT YOUR FATHER
HAS, AND CUT DOWN THE WOODEN image that
is beside it." Look at the next verse.
Everybody read.
"And build an altar to the Lord YOUR GOD
ON TOP OF THIS ROCK IN THE PROPER
ARRANGEMENT. AND TAKE THE SECOND BULL
AND OFFER A BURNT SACRIFICE WITH THE
WOOD of the image WHICH YOU SHALL CUT
DOWN." THE things they were using to
make their gods, that is the wood he
used
for fire.
To show HOW USELESS THEIR GOD IS.
LISTEN, WE ARE COMING FROM A SUPERIOR
KINGDOM.
WE ARE NOT COMING FROM AN INFERIOR
KINGDOM. I AM NOT TEACHING YOU THINGS SO
THAT YOU CAN BE A COWARD. I am teaching
you things SO THAT YOU CAN UNDERSTAND
THERE IS A MILITARY operation that has
been waiting for your manifestation. The
man was told, "Go and take those things,
those gods, those things. Let them
become THE FIRE. LET THEM BE THE ONES TO
CONSUME." SEE WHAT THE BIBLE SAYS.
Go to the next one. Everybody read. "So
Gideon took 10 men from among his
servants." 10 is the number of divine
completion. The reason why you give a
tithe is because that is 10. 10 is the
number of divine completion. "And did as
the Lord had said to him. But because he
feared his father's household and the
men of the city too much to do it by
day, he did it by night." But the truth
is he did it at the end of the day. Look
Look at the next scripture. Whether you
do the operation in the day or at night,
it doesn't matter. "And when the men of
the city arose early in the morning,
there was the altar of Baal torn down,
and the wooden image that was beside it
was cut down, AND THE SECOND BULL was
being offered on the altar WHICH HAD
BEEN BUILT." BEHIND EVERY ALTAR, THERE
IS a household god.
They are gods.
WHEN THE PEOPLE CAME, THEY SAW WHAT HAD
HAPPENED. "AND WHEN THE MEN OF THE CITY
AROSE EARLY, OKAY, CONTINUE. GO TO THE
NEXT VERSE QUICKLY. SO THEY SAID TO ONE
ANOTHER, "WHO HAS done this thing?" AND
WHEN THEY HAD INQUIRED and asked, they
said, "GIDEON, THE SON OF JOASH, HAS
DONE THIS THING." YOU THEY WILL LOOK at
you. They will say, "Rashid, the son of
Pastor Dee, has done THIS THING." WE ARE
RAISING SONS THAT ARE GOING TO DO
THINGS.
NO, I'M NOT THE ONE TO COME TO YOUR
VILLAGE. BY THIS REVELATION, I AM
SENDING YOU TO YOUR VILLAGE. AS A SON OF
THIS HOUSE, YOU ARE GOING WITH THE
ANOINTING OF THE HOLY GHOST IN THE POWER
OF THE NAME OF JESUS AND THE BLOOD OF
YESHUA. YOU DON'T NEED TO RAISE ANOTHER
ALTAR. YOU WILL GO THERE AND PLANT THE
ALTAR OF JESUS, THE COMPLETE WORK OF
CALVARY, THE FINAL SACRIFICE, AND
DECLARE, "AS FOR ME AND MY HOUSE, WE
SHALL SERVE THE LORD. NO MORE IDOL, NO
MORE ALTAR, NO MORE VENERATION OF
ANCESTRAL SPIRITS. WE WILL SERVE THE
LORD AND THE HOLY GHOST."
SO THEY said to one another,
"Who has done this thing?" And when they
had inquired and asked, "Gideon, the son
of Joash." Look at 30.
"Then the men of the city SAID TO JOASH,
"BRING OUT YOUR SON THAT HE MAY DIE,
BECAUSE HE HAS TORN DOWN the altar of
Baal and because he has cut down the
wooden image that was beside it." I love
father of Gideon. "But Joash said to all
who stood against him, "Would you plead
for Baal? Would you save him? If your
god is the real god, let him kill my
son.
WHY ARE YOU FIGHTING FOR YOUR GOD? WOULD
YOU SAVE HIM? LET THE ONE WHO WOULD
PLEAD for him be put to death by
morning. If he is a god,
let him plead for himself because his
altar has been torn down."
DO YOU KNOW ONE THING ABOUT OUR GOD? OUR
GOD DOES NOT NEED YOUR HELP. OUR GOD IS
GOING TO CONFIRM THAT HE'S RESPONSIBLE.
THE BIBLE SAYS ELIJAH SAID, "OH GOD,
BECAUSE YOU ARE GOD, ANSWER BY FIRE."
AND THE LORD ANSWERED BY FIRE. I DECLARE
AS YOU BEGIN THE OPERATION, DIVINE
BACKUP IS YOUR PORTION. WHAT YOUR FATHER
COULD NOT DESTROY, MAY YOU BE THE
GENERATION TO GO AND DESTROY IT. GIDEON
DESTROYED WHAT THE FATHER COULD NOT
DESTROY. WHAT OTHER GENERATION COULD NOT
CONQUER, TODAY I RELEASE THE GRACE OF
GOD. I RELEASE THE POWER AND THE
ANOINTING OF THE HOLY GHOST. ARISE IN
THAT POWER. GO AND BRING DOWN THE ALTARS
THAT HAVE HINDERED YOUR FATHER'S HOUSE.
Bring down the gods.
[Music]
I can tell you something.
I come from a place where I know
some of my relatives and some very close
to me
are now elders among the Kikuyu council.
BUT THEY KNOW I'M A PASTOR.
THERE ARE THINGS THEY CANNOT DO WHEN I'm
there.
Because they know
my god.
And they know
I cannot participate.
AND THEY HAVE SEEN MY GOD.
IF MY ISSUE OF wishing better results
last my issue,
people can argue with YOUR PRAYER.
PEOPLE CAN ARGUE WITH YOUR OFFERING.
PEOPLE CAN ARGUE WITH YOUR TITHE. BUT
PEOPLE CAN NEVER ARGUE WITH YOUR
RESULTS. THE BIBLE SAYS NICODEMUS CAME
TO JESUS BY night and said, "Oh Jesus,
YOU KNOW NO MAN CAN DO THE THINGS YOU
ARE DOING UNLESS THE HAND OF GOD IS UPON
THAT MAN." I WANT TO DECLARE FROM TODAY,
FROM TODAY, YOUR LIFE SHALL BE A LIFE OF
RESULTS. THEY MAY ARGUE WITH YOUR
CHRISTIANITY. THEY MAY CALL IT A WHITE
MAN RELIGION, BUT THEY CANNOT ARGUE WITH
YOUR GOD. THEY CANNOT ARGUE WITH THE
RESULTS IN YOUR LIFE. LIFT UP YOUR HANDS
IN THE NAME OF JESUS. MY LIFE SHALL BE A
LIFE
OF RESULTS. FROM TODAY, I DECLARE I AM A
LIVING EPISTLE. I AM A SIGN AND A
WONDER. THERE ARE RESULTS IN MY LIFE.
ANY MAN THAT WORSHIPS ANOTHER GOD, ANY
ELDERSHIP IN YOUR FATHER'S HOUSE, FROM
THIS HOUR I DECLARE, MAY YOUR GOD ARISE
THAT HIS ENEMIES MAY BE SCATTERED. MAY
THERE BE A DISTINCTION BETWEEN THE
WORSHIPERS OF YAHWEH AND THE WORSHIPERS
OF OTHER GODS. MAY THERE BE A CLEAR
DISTINCTION BETWEEN THEM THAT BOW TO THE
GOD THAT IS ALIVE AND THEM THAT BOW TO
THE MOUNTAIN. FROM TODAY, ANNOUNCE OVER
YOUR LIFE, THERE SHALL BE TANGIBLE
RESULTS. THERE SHALL BE EVIDENCES OF THE
GOD THAT YOU CARRY. MAY IT BE UPON YOU.
THEY MAY ARGUE WITH YOUR THEOLOGY, BUT
THEY CANNOT ARGUE WITH YOUR RESULTS.
I have SEEN SOME OF MY PEOPLE
SUFFERING.
WE HAVE TO BAIL THEM OUT.
YET THEY STILL CRITICIZE OUR GOD.
DISEASES, AFFLICTIONS, POVERTY, CHAOS.
YET THEY STILL COME AND CRITICIZE OUR
GOD. BUT I'M ALWAYS enjoying
when they call
so that I can get at to evangelize
and tell them, the Lord that has lifted
me, may he intervene over your matter.
This God is not a white man. This God is
a spirit.
And you know when a man is in need, he
cannot deny your prayers.
Yeah.
SO, BEFORE YOU SEND THAT MONEY IN THAT
HARAMBEE, begin by prayer.
I SAY, "CAN I PRAY FIRST?"
BECAUSE THEY KNOW YOU ARE BLESSED.
AND they cannot ignore you.
YOU TELL THEM, "CAN I RELEASE A PRAYER?"
BECAUSE THE ONE I SERVE CAN HELP YOU.
YOU DON'T NEED MONEY.
YOU NEED THE ONE THAT I SERVE. THERE
WILL BE a clear distinction.
I say there will be a clear distinction.
That we will not we will not defend
ourselves. The Lord shall arise. THE
LORD SHALL DEFEND HIMSELF. THE ORDERS
ARE COMING DOWN. I SEE THEM. THEY ARE BY
THIS REVELATION, SOMETHING IS being
engineered in YOUR SPIRIT. NO, IT IS NOT
LIFE AS USUAL. THINGS DON'T JUST HAPPEN.
THERE IS SOMETHING CALLED THE LAW OF
CAUSE AND EFFECT. SOMETHING MUST HAPPEN
FOR SOMETHING TO HAPPEN. SO, SOMEBODY
MUST INITIATE ANOTHER ORDER FOR CERTAIN
RESULTS TO BEGIN TO HAPPEN. THERE ARE
CERTAIN ORDERS THAT ARE COMING TO AN
END.
YOU SEE WHEN WHEN Rachel carried the
gods of her father,
the Bible says Laban pursued them.
He pursued them when when when when when
Jacob left WITH HIS WIVES. LABAN PURSUED
THEM. HE CAME AND ASKED JACOB, "HOW CAN
YOU LEAVE WITHOUT EVEN MY BLESSING?"
Because they escaped. BUT HE WAS NOT
COMING TO BLESS HIS CHILDREN. ONE OF THE
DAUGHTERS HAD GONE WITH THE GODS. AND
THE BIBLE SAYS THE FATHER JACOB DID NOT
EVEN KNOW. HE SAID, "YOU CAN SEARCH IN
MY CAMP. WE DIDN'T steal anything from
you. It is you who even oppressed us."
And the Bible says that Rachel sat on
those gods.
MEANING THAT THERE WAS A LEVEL OF
INTERROGATION. THERE are certain areas
the father could not touch the daughter
because she had sat on the god. HOW CAN
YOU SERVE A GOD YOU CAN'T see to?
HOW DO YOU SERVE A GOD YOU NEED TO WASH?
A god you need to feed.
HOW DO YOU SERVE? SO, SHE SAT ON THE
GODS.
THE FATHER SEARCHED AND NEVER FOUND
THEM. But this WAS THE PROBLEM.
RACHEL NEVER truly believed in the god
of Jacob.
SO, THESE ARE THE PEOPLE WHO COME TO
CHURCH, BUT THEY still have connection
to certain orders. Your mother IS STILL
AN ADVISER. AND THEY CALL THEM
traditional doctors.
Is someone getting me?
SO, THERE'S A LEVEL YOU NEED TO REFUSE
THE GODS IN YOUR father's house.
Oh, you know you are GETTING A CHILD.
THIS IS HOW WE USED TO DO in our home.
We need to shave that child. TAKE THE
HAIR TO THE GRANDMOTHER. LISTEN, there
is no hair you are taking to a
grandmother. And this child is not that
grandmother who has been born. This is a
child that has a unique destiny. THIS
CHILD HAS A UNIQUE FUTURE. NOBODY has
been born. THIS IS A SEED THAT CAME FROM
YAHWEH.
YOU CONTEND FOR THAT CHILD. Some rituals
are performed and hijackings happen at
birth.
THINGS ARE DONE OVER A CHILD WHEN THEY
ARE BORN. AND A HIJACKING HAPPENS. AND
BY THE TIME THEY GROW, THEY HAVE TO
WRESTLE WITH THINGS THEY DIDN'T
UNDERSTAND.
And so,
because of that, she never entered her
destiny. Allow me to tell you for free.
You can't serve God and serve orders and
think you'll enter the destiny of God.
The Bible says that Rachel died next to
Bethlehem.
The place that God had chosen to
establish Jacob was Bethlehem.
The labor pains of of Rachel came at the
gate of Bethlehem. She never entered her
prophetic destiny because her trust was
not IN THE LORD. WHY SHOULD I MISS WHAT
GOD has ordained for me because of
things that are made by hands, gods of
WOOD AND IRON, IDOLS THAT CAN NEITHER
speak and CAN NEVER ANSWER? WHY SHOULD I
MISS WHAT GOD has ordained for me? The
Bible says that labor came to her. And
she had to fulfill her assignment,
though she never entered destiny.
Please, you need to understand. There
are certain levels where God will permit
Samson to fulfill assignment, but not
enter destiny.
THE PHILISTINES ARE DEAD.
BUT THAT IS NOT THE DESTINY OF SAMSON.
SO, RACHEL'S ASSIGNMENT WAS TO DELIVER
BENJAMIN, the 12th child in the order of
Jacob, SO THAT NOW JACOB CAN BECOME
ISRAEL. THAT was her assignment. BY THE
TIME SHE FINISHED DELIVERING ASSIGNMENT,
SHE DIED.
MAY THAT NOT BE CAPTURED OVER YOUR LIFE.
YOU WILL NOT JUST FULFILL THE PURPOSES
OF GOD. YOU WILL ALSO ENTER in the place
of your prophetic ordination. I say you
will get into a place of YOUR PROPHETIC
ORDINATION, NOT JUST DOING the
assignment of God.
The Bible says she delivered
and called that child Ben-Oni.
She named the child according to her
situation.
Ben-Oni means the child of my pain.
Because her labor was intensive.
I looked at that child and said, "This
is the child of my pain."
But Jacob grabbed the child
and said, "This cannot be Ben-Oni."
Because the day Jacob met the Lord, he
discovered his life was in a mess
because of a wrong name.
His life was in a mess. He kept on
running and pursuing and fighting for
every BLESSING BECAUSE THE DAY RACHEL
THE DAY REBECCA was pregnant, she
consulted God and she was told there are
two nations. But on the day of delivery,
she never asked God, "What do I name the
nations?" She said, "This is Esau
because he's hairy. And this is Jacob
because he has held the feet of his
brother." So, again, he named the man
after his situation. And that messed up
the destiny OF JACOB. NOW, HERE IS
ANOTHER MOTHER trying to repeat the
error of Jacob's mother. Jacob was too
close to see that ANOTHER GENERATION
WILL NOT BE AFFECTED BY WHAT I FOUGHT.
BY THIS REVELATION, THERE ARE THINGS YOU
ARE UNDERSTANDING. AND THERE ARE PEOPLE
WHO WILL NEVER SUFFER WHAT YOU SUFFERED.
HE LOOKED AT THAT CHILD AND LOOKED AT
HIM AND HE REALIZED, "I, JACOB, HAVE
BEEN A PRODUCT OF A BAD NAME. WHEN I MET
THE LORD, I ASKED HIM, 'LORD, I CAN'T
LEAVE YOU UNTIL YOU BLESS ME.'" And the
Lord asked him, "What is YOUR NAME?" I
THOUGHT, "LORD, YOU ARE GOING TO OPEN
DOORS." THEN THE LORD SAID, "NO, IT'S
NOT ABOUT THE DOORS. IN THIS WRESTLING,
WHAT HAS MESSED YOUR LIFE IS YOUR NAME."
And he said, "IN THE JOURNALS OF
ETERNITY, THERE IS NO MAN LIKE JACOB."
WHEN I LOOK AT THE REGISTER OF HEAVEN,
THE PERSON THAT WAS MEANT TO BE BORN AS
A TWIN of Esau, his name was Israel, NOT
JACOB. BUT THAT NAME HAS COSTED YOUR
DESTINY.
HE LOOKED at that child and said, "No,
this is not Ben-Oni.
This is Benjamin, the child of my right
hand."
What he didn't know,
he was giving prophecy to that child.
Many years later,
Joseph has to enter Egypt.
Jacob is in his old age. The right hand
is the hand of power and strength. IN
THE DAYS OF HIS WEAKNESS, THERE is a
drought. He can't feed his family. In
the DAYS OF HIS WEAKNESS, ONE OF HIS
SONS IS A PRINCE in Egypt. And Joseph
demanded and said, "Until you bring
Benjamin, I cannot do anything." The day
Benjamin showed up, Joseph told the
servants, "Disappear." And he came and
tore his garments because the Egyptians
were not being circumcised. He said, "I
am one of you." And out of Benjamin,
Jacob got his access to Egypt. In his
old age, that son became the support of
his old age. HE WAS NOT JUST seeing a
child. He gave the child a prophetic
name. And that name BECAME A REALITY.
NAMES ARE NOT NAMES. TITLES ARE NOT
TITLES. IDENTITIES are not identities.
Some of us, we are living prophecies. WE
CAME AS AN ANSWER TO A CRY. THE BIBLE
SAYS WHEN THE DAY THE CHILDREN OF ISRAEL
CRIED UNTO THE LORD, THE BIBLE SAYS ON
THAT DAY A LEVITE MAN MET A LEVITE WOMAN
AND MOSES WAS CONCEIVED. SOME OF YOU,
YOU DIDN'T JUST APPEAR AS ANOTHER CHILD.
YOU ARE NOT A SECOND BORN. YOU ARE NOT A
LAST BORN. YOU ARE THE HOPE OF THAT
FAMILY. YOU ARE THE ONE THAT CAME AFTER
YOUR MOTHER CRIED TO ZION AND SAID,
"LORD, WHO SHALL DELIVER US FROM THIS
POVERTY? WHO SHALL CHANGE THE NARRATIVE
OF THESE PATTERNS? WHO SHALL DELIVER US
FROM THESE CURSES?" WHEN THE CRY REACHED
THE HEAVEN, A DELIVERER WAS BORN. THAT
IS WHY YOU'RE IN THE HOUSE OF GOD. THAT
IS WHY YOU LOVE PRAYER. THAT IS WHY YOU
ARE HEARING WHAT YOU ARE HEARING BECAUSE
THIS IS NOT A SERVICE FOR EVERYBODY.
THIS IS A PREPARATION CAMP FOR MEN THAT
ARE GOING BACK TO THEIR HOMES AND BEGIN
TO CAUSE HAVOC AND DELIVER THE FAMILY TO
ELOHIM. I AM SPEAKING TO THE MOSES THAT
ARE HERE. YOU CAME AS AN ANSWER OF A
CRY. THERE ARE MEN THAT MANIFESTED AS AS
responses to tears. We were not born
because a date went wrong. We were born
because order needed to come in our
families. The day your father looked at
the chaos, Gideon had to be born. Lift
up your hand and say in the name of
Jesus, "I WILL FINISH MY ASSIGNMENT AND
ENTER MY DESTINY IN THE MIGHTY NAME OF
JESUS. EVERY HOUSEHOLD IDOL IN MY
FATHER'S HOUSE, YOUR TIME IS OVER.
Praise the Lord.
Generational altars.
[Music]
They cannot go without
generational or household gods.
This
There are certain things
that empower these demonic altars.
that empower them.
I don't even know whether I'll handle
the other topics.
But there are certain things that
empower them.
The first thing that empowers them
is what I call
if you come from a family of occultic
men.
Occultic.
Occultic men.
If you come from a family of occultic
men, what is occultic men?
You see, the the demonic realm is
segregated in different segments.
There are many occults.
There are many.
And these occults
are 100%
demonic centers.
So,
depending with what a man wants from the
kingdom of darkness,
they will always be referred to a
certain occultic order.
So, let's assume you're a politician
and you want political power.
You will be referred to a certain
occultic order
that entices certain spirits that give
men influence in territories.
Let's say you're a businessman
and you want wealth.
They will not refer you where they refer
the politician.
They will refer you to another occultic
order that does rituals that manipulate
spirits that give you advantage in the
marketplace.
Let's assume
uh
you you you are desiring control
of a territory.
And in that control
you become like a principality that when
when when you are touched, the territory
will burn.
They will not refer you to the political
one. They will not refer you to the one
that people get with. They will refer
you to another order where you are now
doing business with spirits of chaos.
That's why there are people you touch
and there is demonic tension.
Because there are certain powers and
altars and systems that support them.
And so, there are many occultic orders.
And sorry to say, some of the young
people are joining some of these orders
unknowingly. You have heard of people
talk of money rituals.
Where people want to do some You you you
want to prosper and you are told, "Oh,
there's a young man we were praying for
and he was told to go to the ocean with
a black sheep
to go and sacrifice it there." And this
is true story. If Pastor Jim was here,
he would have told you. And he was told
to slaughter
in Kenya in the ocean. There was a
priest there and when he slaughtered, he
told me something came, a bag like a
briefcase. He could see the money, but
no one else could see the money.
And so, they were being trained on how
to do money rituals. And he was under a
certain priest. And that PRIEST IS THE
ONE who was telling them what to do.
Sometimes they would be given prayers
or recitations and incantations
which they were supposed to wake UP AT
3:00, FACE A CERTAIN direction and
announce them. And this is what the
young man told us. It was so bad because
he used to love GOING OUT.
SO, ONE DAY HE FORGOT BECAUSE HE IT WAS
LATE. HE WAS DRINKING AND DANCING AND
PEOPLE IN HIS ORDER NEEDED TO DO IT
uniformly at a specific hour.
AND WHEN YOU BYPASS A CERTAIN COMMAND,
THERE ARE CONSEQUENCES.
SO, YOU CAN'T GO OUT. AND THAT TIME IS
WHEN HE DISCOVERED HE HAD JOINED A
demonic thing because he just thought we
go there, pray and play and we make
money. And that's when one of the elders
told him, "SOME OF US HAVE SACRIFICED
OUR children to be here. You can't mess
up the circle."
When he was coming FOR DELIVERANCE, HE
GOT three accidents.
From the TOWN HE WAS COMING FROM, AN
ACCIDENT. SOMETHING would appear on his
forehead
and he would sit ON THE DRIVER AND THE
next thing, accident. By the time THEY
REACHED THE CAR THEY TOOK TO COME TO
LIMURU, they had to use two cars.
So, what happened? We had to hide him in
Christ.
Tell him to take away his physical phone
call, but they will still visit him in
dreams because they had said that now we
want to walk with you up to a certain
age and he had even been shown the girl
he was going to marry, a model in South
Africa. And the kind of things he was
going to do, but this is what he was
told, "Your assignment is not now, but
we can see something in you we want to
use." Because the kingdom of darkness
does not have anything. The Bible says,
"Every good gift and perfect gift comes
from above."
Allow me to speak to the young people.
The greatest thing precious in this life
is your peace.
Peace.
Peace. You can't trade IT FOR ANYTHING.
YOU CAN'T trade it for anything. You
can't. The young man will sleep and say
he HAS NO BLOOD. GO to the hospital, he
has no blood. No coupling because there
are certain blood rituals he entered
into. So, WE ARE SEEING SOME YOUNG
PEOPLE DRIVING MACHINES. SOME OF US KNOW
HOW THE ECONOMY LOOKS AND WHAT IT TAKES
TO BUY A RANGE ROVER, TO BUY AN
ESCALADE. THEY WILL PARADE THE MATERIAL,
BUT WHAT is the cost?
And I'm NOT SAYING YOU CANNOT BE YOUNG
AND PROSPEROUS. DON'T GET ME WRONG. I
KNOW THERE ARE MANY GENUINE ways of
making money, but you cannot wake up
from Narok, A VILLAGE CALLED MAJENGO, IN
LESS THAN 5 YEARS, YOU ARE A MILLIONAIRE
IN RUAKA. WHAT ARE YOU DOING
THAT WE HAVE NOT DONE?
Tell us your secrets. AND WHAT WILL THEY
PARADE? A lifestyle of partying, a
lifestyle of traveling, a lifestyle of
cars, not how they make their money.
AND SOME OF THEM YOU'LL NEVER SEE THEM
SOBER
BECAUSE YOU CAN'T FACE YOURSELF. THE
demonic realm IS SO OPPRESSIVE THAT YES,
YOU LOOK like you have it, but you lost
it. And some don't know even how to get
out because the covenants demand your
life. And one of the ways to get out is
to return everything you have gotten
from the covenant. Are you willing to
sleep down? Are you willing to sleep
hungry? Are you willing to go through a
wilderness for 2 years and suffer?
That's why THE BIBLE SAYS, "WHAT
benefits a man to gain the whole world
and lose his soul?" And this is the
reality. The devil does not play fair.
He will never play fair. AFTER HE'S DONE
USING YOU, he will dump you.
And part of that dumping might be your
own life.
Please tell your neighbor, "Neighbor,
tembea.
Wewe si kilema.
Panda nduthi.
Hakuna hakuna kitu ya maana kama freedom
yako.
Kuliko kuwa uko KWA RANGE ROVER NA SAA
TISA LAZIMA UAMKE uanze ku kupiga
matambiko na kafara ambazo HAZILETI
SENSE. SAA TISA SISI TUNAKUANGA
TUMELALA.
HIYO NDIO MASAA YA MALAIKA. MTU HAEZI
LALA. I'M A PARTY OF MY SCHEDULES IN THE
OCCULTIC BECAUSE YOU CAN'T ENTER. AND
PART OF THAT OCCULTIC opens a door. SO,
IF A MAN PROSPERS BY THE OCCULTIC
SYSTEM, his children must fight the
battle.
And there ARE SONS AND DAUGHTERS WHO ARE
FIGHTING battles and they know the
problem in this house is my father.
Because he's A STRANGE MAN.
THE PROBLEM OF THIS HOUSE IS MY MOTHER.
SHE'S A strange woman. We know.
AND SOME OF THEM ARE BORN AGAIN,
BUT YOU CAN SENSE THERE IS A RIFT.
YOU'LL BE SO SURPRISED. A MAN IN THIS
LAND DISOWNED HIS OWN DAUGHTER BECAUSE
HE GOT born again.
DISOWNED.
AND SAID, "THIS IS NOT MY DAUGHTER." THE
DAUGHTER GOT BORN AGAIN AND GOT MARRIED.
A wealthy man in this land. I know him.
If I mention his name, you'll be
surprised. One of the leading
billionaires disowned.
Because the daughter got born again.
WHAT WAS THAT? THE DAUGHTER HAD entered
a system that can interfere with her
powers.
So, WE CANNOT RELATE BY BLOOD ANYMORE
BECAUSE IN THE HEAVENS, YOU ARE MY
ENEMY. On earth, you are my daughter.
And because of the details of this
covenant, I rather lose my daughter
because the system of darkness has TO
DEHUMANIZE YOU SO THAT NOW YOU CAN
BECOME A TOOL THAT the devil can use.
THAT'S WHY YOU FIND A MAN WHO HAS CARS
PARADED OUTSIDE HIS HOUSE, BUT his
mother is still living in a mud house
because that man is not given wealth to
support his family. He's given wealth so
that his appetites are tested to see how
far he can go.
THE SAME SYSTEM THE DEVIL USED, showed
Jesus THE KINGDOMS,
PARADED IT TO HIM, SHOWED HIM, IS THE
SAME SYSTEM he uses. He will parade
things
and then he will tell you, "Bow down and
worship me and this shall be your
stuff." It's a lie.
History has proved no man bowed and left
with the things of the devil.
No, it's a lie.
I look at some of our musicians and my
heart cries for them.
SOME OF THEM THEY ARE fame hungry that a
man can produce a song that looks like
pornography so that men can talk. That
is the appetite of fame.
And what WHAT AND I'LL SHOW IT BY THIS
SCRIPTURE. WHAT THAT YOUNG MAN DOES NOT
KNOW, HE COULD BE OPENING A DOOR OF
INIQUITY FOR HIS OWN CHILDREN.
HE MAY NOT PAY THE PRICE, BUT HIS
CHILDREN MIGHT BE THE ONE TO SUFFER. SO,
IT IS A SERIOUS MATTER. WE DON'T LIVE
FOR OURSELVES. WE DON'T LIVE FOR CROWNS.
WE LIVE FOR JESUS. THERE ARE THINGS YOU
DO, THEY MAY NOT AFFECT YOU BECAUSE YOU
BECAME A TOOL THAT the devil can use,
BUT YOU HAVE OPENED A LEGALITY IN THE
SPIRIT. HAVE YOU NOT REALIZED THAT SOME
WOMEN PARTICIPATE IN PROSTITUTION, THEN
THEY OPEN A DOOR OF PERVERSION TO THEIR
DAUGHTERS AND SONS?
BY THE TIME YOU GIVE BIRTH TO A CHILD,
HE'S NOW GOING TOWARD LGBTQ, but when
you look at your past, THERE ARE CERTAIN
TRANSACTIONS YOU ARE participating in
and they open A LEGALITY. SO, THAT
SPIRIT WANTS TO RECRUIT EVERYONE. I saw
that video. I SAW IT. I BEGAN TO
INTERCEDE for the brother BECAUSE IN HIS
IGNORANCE, HE MAY NOT KNOW. HE WILL GET
A MILLION VIEWS, BUT HE MAY NOT KNOW THE
REPERCUSSIONS IN THE REALMS OF THE
SPIRIT, NOT JUST FOR OUR GENERATION, FOR
HIS OWN FAMILY. AND WHAT I CAN TELL HIM,
BECAUSE OF THE REVIVAL THAT IS COMING
UPON KENYA, SOME OF THOSE STAFFS, they
will BE JUDGED HIGHLY.
THEY WILL BE JUDGED HIGHLY. I STAND
UNDER THE ANOINTING TO TELL YOU, GOD IS
JEALOUSY ABOUT THIS GENERATION. I HAVE
SEEN. I HAVE PROPHESIED AND I CAN
PROPHESY AGAIN. There are people who
began things during COVID. JUDGMENT CAME
UPON THEM. THAT HAND OF JUDGMENT IS
STILL UPON THIS LAND.
AND I I PLEAD FOR MERCY BECAUSE MY JOY
IS NOT WHEN JUDGMENT LANDS ON A MAN. I
PLEAD FOR MERCY. I PLEAD for mercy
because I know his heart.
Generational iniquity will touch that
thing.
There are things the devil will initiate
you to do, but they don't just affect
you.
You you might think you are just opening
a bar.
The next thing all your children die of
alcohol.
You you just You're just doing a wine
and spirit business. You don't drink.
You even tithe.
By the time you are 50, 60, all your
children are in rehab.
But pastor, people are doing that
business. You need to understand not
every door is your door.
Not every business is YOUR BUSINESS. NOT
EVERY CAREER IS your career.
These are some of the things people did
and now we have to pay prices
because someone was careless on a
certain depth transaction.
Somebody say they are cultic.
Am I speaking to anyone? Some of our
uncles are deep in this stuff.
We know.
They keep on sacrificing family members
every year.
But they cannot touch you. Do you know
that?
They can't touch you.
If you see YOURSELF IN THE SPIRIT, YOU
ARE ALWAYS GUARDED BY FIRE.
THAT'S THE REALITY.
DON'T THINK THE PRAYERS WE ARE MAKING
HERE ARE ORDINARY.
I know a lady who used to come here for
church. The husband told her, "Don't go
to that church.
Every time you pray, something burns in
my house."
I was very happy when I heard that
report
because I didn't know who are BURNING
HOUSES.
THE MAN DID NOT HAVE A PROBLEM FOR HER
TO GO IN SOME CERTAIN CHURCHES. There
was no problem.
But the man and he's a political He has
He had a problem for the lady to come
here because every time Pastor Eugene is
saying in the name of Jesus, something
is burning on another man's house. Allow
me to tell you, from today, YOU ARE NOT
RISING afraid of these men. LET THE MAN
SERVE HIS ALTAR. YOU ALSO SERVE YOUR
ALTAR. LET THE STRONGEST ALTAR CONTEND
FOR THIS FAMILY.
LET THE STRONGEST ONE CONTEND. I HAVE
MET MEN OF THE DARK WORLD. THEY KNOW US.
THEY KNOW US.
SOME OF THEM CANNOT EVEN FACE YOU FOR 2
MINUTES.
I HAVE SAT IN COUNCILS AND I CAN ADD,
"THIS ONE IS FROM ANOTHER ORDER." AND
WHAT I LIKE DOING, I look them straight
in the EYE BECAUSE THE BIBLE SAYS WE ARE
FLAMES in the spirit. So, I look them
STRAIGHT IN THE EYE BECAUSE THE EYES ARE
GATE OF YOUR SPIRIT. WHEN THEY LOOK at
you, they don't SEE A YOUNG GIRL. THEY
BEGIN TO SEE SOMETHING BURNING. NO
DETAILS. YOU ARE HIDDEN UNDER THE CLOUDS
OF THE MOST HIGH. THEY HAVE NO PATTERN,
NO DETAIL AND THEY BEGIN TO ASK, "WHO is
this?"
IN THIS FAMILY, EVERYONE IS UNDER MY
AUTHORITY. WHO IS THIS YOUNG GIRL? THIS
YOUNG GIRL IS A WORSHIPER. THIS YOUNG
GIRL IS AN INTERCESSOR. THIS YOUNG GIRL
IS A DELIVERER. THIS YOUNG BOY IS THE
GIDEON OF THIS HOME.
HE MAY NOT HAVE THE CAR YOU HAVE, BUT HE
HAS AN ANOINTING TO DELIVER THE FAMILY.
HE MAY NOT CARRY THE WEALTH YOU HAVE
FROM THE DEMONIC, BUT HE HAS AN
ANOINTING TO SHIFT THE TANGENT OF THE
FAMILY AND SHIFT THEM TO THE LIVING GOD.
WE ARE not ordinary.
YEAH.
A MAN WENT AND HE SAW HIS FATHER
PRAYING.
THEN HE SAW SOMETHING LIKE smoke on his
head. The father asked him, "Have you
seen it?" He said, "Yes." He said,
"That's the angel that fights for me."
Some of us we have backup of angels.
YOU MAY NOT SEE THEM BECAUSE OF YOUR
FAITH, BECAUSE YOU WILL WORSHIP THEM,
BUT THEY ARE YOUR SERVANTS. EVERYWHERE
YOU GO, THEY MUST CARRY YOU. THEY MUST
BE WITH YOU. THERE'S A TIME THE LORD
OPENED MY EYES and showed me two angels
in a vision because he I was I was I was
praying AND I SAW AN ANGEL STAND there
and another one stand there and there
were many men and then I was addressing
a matter in the spirit. It was in a
vision. And I realized there are two
angels according to my life because of
the assignment and because of the work.
I'VE NEVER SEEN THEM, BUT I KNOW THEY
ARE THERE BECAUSE there is a level YOU
MUST ENTER WITH BOLDNESS. IT DOES NOT
TAKE ANTHONY to enter. THERE MUST BE A
BACKUP OF HEAVEN WHERE THE WITNESSES OF
GLORY ARE CHEERING UP AND SAYING, "WE
ARE with you." Paul, Peter looking and
saying, "Continue. Continue." That's the
gospel.
THAT'S WHY THERE ARE THINGS that cannot
be penetrated.
DON'T THINK THEY HAVE NOT TRIED. THEY
HAVE TRIED. THERE ARE MANY BATTLES GOD
FIGHTS FOR US WITHOUT telling us.
THERE ARE MANY VICTORIES HE GIVES US
WITHOUT TELLING US. Sometimes you're
just sensitive in the spirit and you
sense, "I cannot go to town." That was
the day to get an accident. Sometimes
you just feel, "No, no, I DON'T KNOW
WHY, BUT I NEED to pray." THAT IS THE
TIME YOU are invoking divine backup. May
you be sensitive in THE SPIRIT. THE
WORLD IS NOT THE WORLD YOU USED TO KNOW
A FEW YEARS AGO. MEN CAN DO ANYTHING TO
GET wealth and we will do EVERYTHING TO
GET THE POWER of God.
So, there are many young people in this
nation
in the occultic.
Some are old.
And it is out of that occultic order
that now you come to the second phase,
which is where now you have the
whatever they call them,
Freemasons. Still an order.
Many of the Freemasons operate in
families.
You don't just go as a man.
The greatest initiation you can do is
that of a family.
I was in America and we were worshipping
and there was a Freemason chapel there.
They they they they want to transfer
that thing to their children. That's
generational heritage. So, you'll hear
someone say, "My grandfather was a
Mason. My father is a Mason and now they
want to recruit me into Masonry." And
they go with their children the way we
come with our children to church. It's
an order.
And and and And let me tell you the
truth. The the ranks of the Masons The
ranks of the Masons is a is a coded
because in every rank, there are certain
performances that are needed and some of
their activities and rituals, some of
them mirror our Bible. Even some of
their language, they will talk about
ordination. They will talk about baptism
into a new order because it is a
spiritual language.
And I can tell you for free,
one of the thing that gives the church
disadvantage is lack of seriousness and
commitment and discipline. When men join
some of these orders, the level of
discipline that is needed and
commitment, a man that is in a 33rd
degree level of the Mason cannot even
share the secrets of his performances
and rituals to a man that is in a 10th
or second degree. Though they're in the
same fellowship, you can't share because
everything is a secret. That's why it's
a secret society.
That we're IN THE SAME FELLOWSHIP, BUT
WHAT I DO as rituals in my rank to gain
that rank, I can't tell you.
I HAVE VOWED WITH MY NECK. LET A SWORD
COME from my ear to my ear. That's the
vow they sign and take me off if I share
some of those things. That's the vow
they take.
So, we don't pray.
And in sealing those vows, there are
certain demands that they must meet. You
don't GET TO A CERTAIN LEVEL without
meeting certain demands. And so, if you
come from a family that has certain
connections in that area, it means
that's a living altar.
Am I speaking to anyone?
If you come from a family
where there are witches and witchcraft
is alive, that's a living altar.
Wizards, witches, sorcerers, they are
all there.
Grandmother, AUNTIES, UNCLES,
SOME HAVE ALTARS IN RUNDA, big mansions,
but there's a room only a man enters.
THERE ARE CERTAIN RELIGIONS WHERE MEN
ARE PERMITTED TO raise genies.
It's in their theology.
Genies are marine kingdom spirits.
And I'm For those who have worked in
Saudi Arabia and those some of those
nations, YOU THERE IS A MAIN HOUSE, BUT
THERE IS AN ALTAR OUTSIDE. And it's only
the man that enters to service the
altar.
[Music]
You know, some of us our connections are
multicultural.
Christian, Hindu, Muslim, you know. So,
by default you have to get a few
intelligences.
So, you go to a room and there's a room
you cannot enter. No man enters that
room because it's an altar in that
house.
Hm.
That's why there are certain events you
go and the Holy Ghost will tell you
don't eat.
Because before they serve, they took it
to their gods.
So, that food is not a meal. It's an
initiation and a hijacking. And I'm not
selling fear.
That's why YOU MUST BE ALERT
IN THE SPIRIT.
Not every baby shower and every birthday
you go there with appetite.
There's a bond of
Some of them you enter,
you look at the decor,
you begin to see signs,
colors, arrangements, programming,
language, you know, no. This is not a
baby shower. We have entered a space in
the spirit.
[Music]
You know, it's our spiritual ignorance.
People parade their stuff
all over.
It's a home dedication,
but you get in that house,
you look at some idols, positioning of
something they are calling art.
And your spirit begins to fringe
BECAUSE YOU CARRY A WITNESS IN YOUR
SPIRIT THAT can tell you this is God and
this is not God. That's why now you just
need to be a PRAYERFUL PERSON
SO THAT WHEN YOU GET IN AN ENVIRONMENT,
you can smile and say, "I have entered a
strange territory, but I'm also a
strange man."
I know SOMEONE WHO WAS WORKING. WHEN THE
PERSON WAS WAKING WAITING ON THE ON THE
ON THE PHOTOCOPIER, some documents came.
Then he saw a demonic logo.
AND THEN THE MANAGER CAME DOWN. HE WAS
THE ONE printing and he realized the
girl has seen the documents.
And immediately there was tension and
the girl lost her job.
[Music]
Because now you have known our secret.
Why should we keep you?
But if you ask me, that was the Lord
setting the girl
to know where she's working.
May the Lord reveal
anything that is hidden.
May the Lord reveal.
I say may the Lord reveal.
Can we even go further?
You know, some some of the people I
remember a girl we told him to marry her
first.
A girl.
The grandmother was in a certain order.
She came and gave her a water dispenser
as a gift.
And she kept on asking,
"Are you using the dispenser?"
So, that was a point of contact. AS LONG
AS they were taking water from the
dispenser, they could not conceive.
Because the grandmother wanted to
release the spirit of shame
by tying the womb of the girl.
That's why when you receive wedding
gifts,
hey,
after honeymoon,
come with anointing oil
and say, "Anointing, IN THE NAME OF
JESUS, IF THERE BE A STRANGE GIFT,
BREAK."
A PREACHER WAS GIVEN A WATCH.
A PREACHER.
AND HE PUT IT ON HIS SITTING ROOM.
AND THAT WATCH WAS A SIGN THAT HE'S
MONITORED. ONE DAY HE PRAYED AT THREE,
THE LORD TOLD HIM, "GET remove that
watch.
It was NOT A GIFT. THAT WAS A TOOL TO
MONITOR YOU."
SO, SOMEONE IS TRAVELING AND IS GIVING
YOU ALL MANNER OF GIFTS. OH, he brought
me a golden chain.
A lady once gave me a silver chain
that had a palm tree.
And she bound me sexually.
I was born again.
I was tired. I could not leave her.
BUT THE SPIRIT, ONE DAY I WAS IN THE
BATHROOM AND I BEGAN TO pray in tongues.
It was on a Sunday. That thing broke.
The next thing I found two missed calls
from her
saying,
"Uh you know, I just feel like we need
to stop this thing."
So, it was not a chain.
[Music]
You know, sometimes you become
vulnerable tell you stories that are not
very good
just to tell you in life be as it may be
here.
Are you getting me?
Anything you receive,
sanctified.
If your spirit rejects,
please.
A lady came and insisted. She came in a
meeting I was preaching with a BUNCH OF
SOCKS.
BYPASSED EVERY PROTOCOL
AND SAID, "I want to give Pastor T
socks."
I can NEVER LET HER. MY WIFE SAW HER.
[Music]
SO, SHE DIDN'T KNOW WHAT I WAS GOING TO
DO WITH THE SOCKS. MAYBE TO control my
walk, I don't know. BUT AT THE END OF
THE DAY, WE HAD TO THROW THEM.
ONE DAY I'M OUT OF THE COUNTRY AND
SOMEONE BRINGS ME NYAMA CHOMA.
[Music]
I CAN NEVER LET HER. I HAVE YOUR GIFT,
but I'm not giving you. I can never let
HER IN HERE.
I'M SORRY TO SAY,
SHE WAS A MEMBER IN CHURCH.
Speaking in tongues.
I'll not say many things.
Nyama, food covenant.
[Music]
Picture is a tribe.
We prayed for a girl
in the mountain.
She vomited rice.
Pray I eat here there.
A brother from a certain religion took
her for a date.
So, it was not mchele anywhere. It was a
covenant in that food.
And the day she vomited that rice, she
got married.
But I'm trying to share something. Tell
your neighbor, "Neighbor,
a radical breed is rising.
We will not be casual with OUR
SPIRITUALITY. WE WILL NOT BE CASUAL WITH
OUR GOD. WE WILL NOT BE CASUAL WITH OUR
OPERATIONS BECAUSE WE UNDERSTAND IT IS
NOT BUSINESS AS USUAL. HALLELUJAH. AND
SO, THOSE PEOPLE THAT ARE IN YOUR FAMILY
EXERCISING A CERTAIN PRIESTHOOD, PEOPLE
THAT ARE USING CERTAIN POWERS, WE WANT
TO DECLARE THEIR TIME HAS COME TO AN
END. ANOTHER ORDER OF PRIEST IS RISING
FROM THE ORDER OF YESHUA. WE HAVE NEVER
LOST ANY BATTLE. WE COME IN THE NAME OF
THE LORD. ANY ALTAR THAT SPEAKS IN YOUR
FATHER'S HOUSE, LET IT COME TO AN END.
ANY DEMONIC OPERATION THAT HAS BEEN
HAPPENING IN YOUR HOME, WE ARE BRINGING
IT TO AN END. PASTOR, WHAT DO I DO
BECAUSE I KNOW THESE THINGS ARE IN MY
FATHER'S HOUSE? THERE IS NOTHING YOU
NEED TO DO. THAT IS THE GOOD NEWS. WHY?
JESUS KNEW THE KINGDOM OF DARKNESS WILL
BE THERE. HE KNEW THERE WILL BE A
PRIEST, THERE WILL BE AN ALTAR, AND
THERE WILL BE A SACRIFICE. BECAUSE HE
KNEW THEY WILL BE THERE, HE KNEW YOU ARE
NOT SUFFICIENT ENOUGH TO WIN THAT
BATTLE. SO, WHAT DID THE LORD JESUS DO?
THE LORD BECAME THE PRIEST IN THE ORDER
OF MELCHIZEDEK. LATER, HE BECAME THE
SACRIFICE, THE LAMB OF GOD, AND CALVARY
BECAME THE MOUNTAIN AND THE ALTAR WHERE
HE WAS SACRIFICED. SO, THE LORD HIMSELF
SHED HIS OWN BLOOD. WHERE THEY ARE
SHEDDING THE BLOOD OF BULLS, WHERE THEY
ARE SHEDDING THE BLOOD OF ANIMALS, IN
THE REALMS OF THE SPIRIT, THE BLOOD THAT
IS THE HIGHEST AND ABOVE ANY OTHER BLOOD
IS NOT EVEN THE BLOOD OF CHILDREN. THEY
CAN GIVE HUMAN SACRIFICE, BUT THERE IS
ONE BLOOD THAT WAS SHED ONCE AND FOR
ALL. ALLOW ME TO GIVE YOU THE GOOD NEWS.
THE BLOOD WAS NOT SHED IN A TIME. THE
BIBLE SAYS BEFORE THE FOUNDATIONS OF THE
EARTH, THE LAMB HAD ALREADY BEEN SLAIN.
BEFORE YOUR GREAT-GRANDMOTHER
BECAME A WITCH AND DISCOVERED HOW TO
SLAUGHTER, THE BLOOD HAD ALREADY BEEN
SHED. BEFORE YOUR UNCLE ENTERED INTO THE
OCCULTIC AND GAVE A CHILD AS A
SACRIFICE, THE BLOOD HAD ALREADY BEEN
SHED. BEFORE THEY GATHERED BECAUSE THEY
WANT TO BRING YOU DOWN AND SACRIFICED A
BULL AND GAVE MONEY, THERE IS BLOOD THAT
CANNOT BE CORRUPTED, NEITHER CAN IT BE
PURCHASED. IT WAS SHED MORE THAN 2,000
YEARS AGO, AND THE BIBLE SAYS THE BLOOD
SPEAKETH BETTER THINGS THAN THE BLOOD OF
BULLS, THAN THE BLOOD OF PHARAOH, THAN
THE BLOOD OF AARON. THERE IS ANOTHER
BLOOD. PLEASE TURN TO THAT NEIGHBOR,
TELL THAT NEIGHBOR, "NEIGHBOR, WE ARE IN
A COVENANT WHERE GOD HAS DONE ON
SO, WHAT DO I DO? WHERE THERE IS A
GENERATIONAL ALTAR, YOU DON'T NEED TO
RAISE ANOTHER ALTAR. YOU DON'T NEED TO
RELEASE A SACRIFICE UNLESS INSTRUCTED BY
GOD.
[Music]
SO, I'M NOT TELLING YOU TO GO AND LOOK
FOR WOOD AND LOOK FOR STONES AND THEN
COME AND LOOK FOR 70,000 AND TAKE A
BULL. NO. IF I TELL YOU THAT, I'LL BE
MAKING YOU A WITCH. I AM TELLING YOU TO
LEAVE THIS HOUSE IN FAITH. I AM TELLING
YOU TO LEAVE IT IN FAITH. KNOW THAT MY
REDEEMER LIVETH. THE ONE THAT I SERVE IS
NOT A DEAD GOD. THE ONE THAT I CALL UPON
IS NOT A DEAF GOD. HIS EYES ARE UPON THE
RIGHTEOUS. HIS EARS ARE ATTENTIVE
ANYTIME THEY CALL. ANYTIME WE CRY, HE
CAPTURES OUR TEARS IN A BOTTLE. HE IS
ALIVE AND HE'S THE ONE THAT IS ALIVE
FOREVERMORE. IN THE BOOK OF REVELATION,
HE SAID, "I AM THE ONE THAT WAS DEAD,
BUT NOW I AM ALIVE AND ALIVE
FOREVERMORE." HE IS THE PRIEST IN THE
ORDER OF MELCHIZEDEK. THEY HAVE A PRIEST
THAT CAN DIE. OUR PRIEST WILL NEVER DIE.
HE'S AN EVERLASTING PRIEST. THE PRIEST
IN YOUR FATHER'S HOUSE, THAT PRIEST CAN
DIE. THAT MAN IS NOT AN ETERNAL MAN. HE
HAS TIME NUMBERED OVER HIS LIFE, BUT WE
HAVE ANOTHER PRIEST WHO LIVES FOREVER.
THEIR ALTAR CAN BE ABANDONED, BUT WE
HAVE ONE THAT MAKES INTERCESSION FOR US
EVERY DAY. HALLELUJAH. AND THEN WE HAVE
THE BEST SACRIFICE, THE LAMB OF GOD. THE
LAMB OF GOD. LET NO ONE DECEIVE YOU. YOU
DON'T NEED TO GIVE A MILLION. YOU DON'T
NEED TO GIVE 100,000. YOU DON'T NEED TO
DO ALL THOSE GIMMICKS. JUST BELIEVE.
JUST BELIEVE. JUST BELIEVE. WHEN YOU GO
BACK TO YOUR FATHER'S HOUSE, ENTER INTO
THAT HOUSE AND SAY, "I COME IN THE NAME
OF THE LORD, THE CREATOR OF THE HEAVENS
AND THE EARTH. I COME IN THE ORDER OF
MELCHIZEDEK, THE PRIEST WHO DOES NOT
DIE. I COME BY THE BLOOD OF YESHUA. I
NOW BRING THE ALTAR OF CALVARY INTO MY
FATHER'S HOUSE. ANY OTHER ALTAR, I
SILENCE YOU FROM NOW. YOU HAVE NO POWER.
YOU HAVE NO VOICE. YOU HAVE NO
AUTHORITY. LEAVE MY FAMILY. RELEASE MY
MOTHER. RELEASE MY BROTHER. RELEASE MY
SISTER. RELEASE MY COUSINS. WHATEVER YOU
CAME TO DO, YOUR TIME IS OVER." AND
BEGIN TO PRAY IN THE HOLY GHOST.
PROCLAIM THE MATTER IN THE SPIRIT. THIS
IS OUR REDEMPTION AND THIS IS OUR
VICTORY. WE COME IN THE NAME OF THE
LORD. I SAY WE COME IN THE NAME OF THE
LORD AND I'M DECLARING TODAY, THE
ANOINTING OF GIDEON IS COMING UPON SOME
OF YOU. IT IS NOT BUSINESS AS USUAL.
WHATEVER THAT YOUR FATHER COULD NOT
DESTROY, RECEIVE THE OIL TO DESTROY IT
RIGHT NOW. I DECLARE EVERY WITCH IN OUR
HOMES, WE ARE GIVING THEM TWO OPTIONS.
IT'S EITHER THEY REPENT OR THEY PERISH.
IT IS EITHER MERCY OR JUDGMENT. ANYONE
THAT HAS CAUSED HAVOC, PEOPLE THAT GO TO
STRANGE ALTARS, FROM THIS HOUR WE
DECLARE, LET THE FIRE OF JUDGMENT AND
THE SWORD OF THE LORD BE STRETCHED UPON
THE ALTAR. WE WILL NOT BURY ANOTHER
FAMILY MEMBER. THERE ARE PEOPLE HERE,
YOU HAVE BEEN IN A CYCLE OF BURIALS. IT
LOOKS LIKE EVERY MONTH, THERE IS A
SPECIFIC MONTH WHERE SOMEBODY MUST DIE.
FROM THIS HOUR WE DECLARE, THE BURIALS
ARE SUSPENDED. NO ONE ELSE WILL DIE.
PEOPLE THAT SURVIVE BY GIVING HUMAN
SACRIFICE, WE RELEASE ANOTHER ORDER.
THIS TIME, YOU WILL NOT RELEASE ANOTHER
SACRIFICE. IT'S EITHER YOU REPENT OR YOU
BECOME THE SACRIFICE. SHATABAKATALIA.
RAPAZETALIA.
MANDELIBRA TALIA. PEOPLE IN THE OCCULTIC
WORLD, PEOPLE THAT HAVE ALTARS WHERE
THEY STAND ON, THEY ADDRESS THEIR
MATTER. WE ARE HERE TO DECLARE, WE ARE
STANDING ON OUR ALTAR. YOU CANNOT
BEWITCH US. YOU CANNOT SHORTCHANGE US.
YOU CANNOT TAKE AWAY OUR DESTINY. YOU
CANNOT ATTACK US. WE ARE SURROUNDED BY
THE FIRE OF THE HOLY GHOST. WE ARE
SURROUNDED BY THE HEDGE OF THE BLOOD OF
YESHUA. THE ANGELS OF YOUR DESTINY, LET
THEM BE DEPLOYED RIGHT NOW. I RELEASE
THE ANGELS CONNECTED TO YOUR ASSIGNMENT
AND CONNECTED TO YOUR DESTINY. ANY POWER
THAT HAS BEEN STANDING AGAINST YOUR
PATH, LET IT LOSE ITS HOLD.
[Music]
THE GODS IN MY FATHER'S HOUSE.
SOMETIMES THEY WAIT FOR US
[Music]
during ruracio's
to introduce the gods.
[Music]
From today,
don't go for that ruracio alone.
Look for men of the spirit.
[Music]
Let your uncle be there,
but look for the one that is born again.
Because they are now waiting for us
during ruracio,
waiting for us during
boy's circumcisions
so that they can now initiate us.
That's why the church must take charge
of the knife
and begin to take care of that gate so
that we don't raise our boys in Sunday
school and one event transitions them
into another order. We are going to
raise a radical breed.
WE BETTER HAVE ELDERS WHO THEIR MAIN
WORK IS to go for ruracio
and they go with the Bible
and they get inside and say, "THIS ONE
IS A CHILD OF THE ALTAR.
WE CAN'T ALLOW NOW
TO SERVE AN ALTAR
OF POLYGAMY. WE WILL FIGHT FOR THAT
GATE.
IT WE MUST BE RADICAL. IS SOMEONE
GETTING ME? WE MUST BE RADICAL WITH OUR
STUFF. YOUR DESTINY WILL NOT BE
HIJACKED. I SAY NO GATE, NO GATE THAT
THE ENEMY HAS BEEN USING, THE GATE OF
BIRTH, THE GATE OF CIRCUMCISION, THE
GATE OF MARRIAGE, THOSE GATES ARE
SECURED FROM NOW. THEY WILL NOT BE
HIJACKED IN THE MIGHTY NAME OF JESUS.
YOUR DESTINY SECURED IN THE NAME OF
JESUS.
[Music]
AS the Lord
released
an anointing upon Gideon
and boldness,
may you be the one to conquer.
I want the ushers to to give us elements
of bread because we are agreeing
with the realities of the blood of
Yeshua.
Hallelujah.
Allow me to say this.
As we are hearing these messages,
the Lord can give instructions,
BUT THOSE INSTRUCTIONS ARE not
doctrines.
I have to stick to the BIBLE
AND MY ASSIGNMENT IS TO MAKE SURE THAT
you know the voice of God.
Because there are certain demands that
God might tell someone, "You need to go
and fast for 40 days OR CERTAIN DAYS."
NOT because he cannot deliver,
but it's because there is an instruction
tied to a certain operation.
Some people GOD MIGHT EVEN TELL THEM,
"You need to release a certain
sacrifice."
IT IS NOT THAT IS NOT A DOCTRINE. IT'S A
PERSONAL INSTRUCTION. When it comes to
the deliverances of families, it is as
unique as that family.
And the Lord can GIVE DIFFERENT DEMANDS.
GIDEON WAS told to go and destroy the
altar. Build another altar. Use whatever
WAS THERE, BUT BECAUSE THE MAN DID NOT
HAVE MONEY, HE WENT for the bulls of HIS
FATHER.
MEANING THAT THERE WAS A SACRIFICE
INVOKED. Is someone getting me?
The Lord can even allow that out of this
atmosphere, the yokes are broken
without doing anything. THAT JUST THE
YOKES AND THE BURDENS ARE LIFTED.
DELIVERANCE IS a mystery.
AND HOW THE LORD MOVES IN THE LIVES OF
MEN is different. Are we together?
Are we together? So, IF THE LORD GIVES
YOU AN INSTRUCTION, PLEASE OBEY.
IF THE LORD PLACES A DEMAND OVER YOUR
LIFE, PLEASE OBEY.
I REMEMBER PASTOR ANITA,
they went with one of our
prayer friends.
THEY WENT TO THEIR VILLAGE
AND THE LORD TOLD THE WOMAN of God,
"THIS IS NOT A TREE.
BEHIND THIS TREE, THERE are things that
were buried."
So, they had to UPROOT THE TREE.
THEY GOT THE STUFF,
BURNT THEM, AND POVERTY LEFT THAT HOME.
SO, THE LORD CAN OPEN YOUR EYES.
I have even had MEN WHO ARE TAKEN TO THE
GRAVES OF THEIR parents
to go and make certain declarations.
I remember there's A HOUSE WE WENT AND
THE YOUNG MAN WAS BOUND WITH ALCOHOL.
THEY TOOK HIM TO REHAB, NOTHING COULD
HAPPEN.
THEN WE WERE TOLD TO GO AND PRAY FOR
HIM. WHEN WE PRAYED FOR HIM, THE LORD
REVEALED TO ME AND HE SHOWED me the
grave of his grandfather.
And I asked the I stopped the prayers. I
asked, "Who is the grandfather of this
guy?
Because the grandfather is responsible."
The mother began to cry.
He said the grandfather used to drink
with him.
They will The grandfather will sit
outside and he will give him to taste
and they will just enjoy. And this was
the favorite son of the grandfather. So,
what was the grandfather doing? He was
initiating the young boy into
alcoholism.
And then I saw that that horn.
And then I was told, "That's what they
used to drink with." So, now we had to
address the man from the grave.
And had to address the man from the
grave.
And address his spirit.
And the man was named AFTER HIS
GRANDFATHER. AND THAT WAS the
deliverance of that man. So, what I'm
TRYING TO SAY, THERE WILL BE
REVELATIONS.
There is NO CONFRONTATION WITHOUT
REVELATION. TWO THINGS ARE GOING TO
HAPPEN. THERE WILL be revelations AND
AUTHORIZATIONS.
PLEASE, DON'T be excited unless the Lord
authorizes a battle. DON'T BEGIN A
BATTLE UNLESS YOU'RE AUTHORIZED.
SO, THERE WILL BE REVELATIONS. SOME OF
YOU AT THE NIGHT HOUR, you'll begin TO
SEE THINGS.
VISIONS AND DREAMS CHANNELS OF
REVELATION. THE MOMENT YOU SEE THEM,
PRAY THAT THE HOLY GHOST GIVES YOU
UNDERSTANDING BECAUSE YOUR DELIVERANCE
IS IN UNDERSTANDING.
I WAS PRAYING FOR OUR FAMILY. I I LOOKED
AT MY FAMILY, ONE SIDE OF MY FAMILY. I
realized that poverty in that side was
not ordinary.
And so, I decided to do some
investigation. Then I met my cousin.
My cousin was doing 40 days of prayer.
And she came and told me, "You know,
as I was praying,
the Lord showed me
our grandfather and he showed me him
hiding money in a garden
as a form of ritual.
And I looked at that
order of my grandfather and his sons.
And I can tell you,
very few have broken
that thing. And the only person who
broke it
is my father.
And he broke it because
one, he gave land to church and he
became generous.
The man I saw in the spirit,
in the day when he died, he died with
money in his pocket. Yet, there was no
shopping at home. THERE WAS A SPIRIT OF
HOARDING.
AND SO, IN SUCH a level, the Lord might
raise a generous man to break certain
cycles because there are certain
principles in the spirit.
May I I said none of us come from a
perfect home.
Is someone getting me?
IN THIS NEXT WEEK, and I bless the Lord
Docuser is here.
SO, SO AND WE ARE COMING TO A SEASON of
looking unto Jesus. May this become the
week of your deliverance.
I say may this become the week of your
deliverance.
And church, let me tell you something.
Allow me to say this.
If I were you,
I will apply for a leave
from Thursday.
I will not allow people who are not sons
of the house to be blessed yet the
conference is organized for me.
That is the error we do.
YOU CAN CLOSE YOUR BUSINESS FOR 4 days,
but the GRACE YOU WILL GET WILL CARRY
YOU FOR 10 YEARS.
Whatever you are meant to make in 4
days, YOU CANNOT COMPARE TO WHAT YOU CAN
GET A DOWNLOAD OF THE SPIRIT. One day in
the Lord is worth A THOUSAND DAYS
ELSEWHERE.
THAT'S THE CALCULATION OF DAVID. PLEASE,
tell tell to that neighbor tell that
neighbor there are times
where our matters must BE URGENT.
TAKE THESE 4 DAYS, PLACE a demand of a
glory.
THERE IS SOMETHING THAT HAPPENS. EVERY
PREACHER IS A CARRIER OF A GRACE.
THERE ARE THINGS I CARRY. THERE ARE
THINGS REVEREND JULIAN CARRIES. THERE
ARE THINGS APOSTLE Juma carries. THERE
ARE THINGS PASTOR MORRIS CARRIES. There
are THINGS PROPHET MANIKI CARRIES. THERE
ARE THINGS BISHOP JB CARRIES. THERE ARE
THINGS PASTOR KEMADI CARRIES. SO, IN
SUCH A CONGLOMERATION, I BELIEVE YOU
cannot miss one MAN THAT HAS CARRIED
SOMETHING THAT IS YOURS.
IF YOU CAN, DON'T WATCH ONLINE.
TELL YOUR NEIGHBOR, "NEIGHBOR,
IMPARTATIONS ARE PHYSICAL."
PREPARE TO RECEIVE.
4 DAYS CAN CHANGE YOUR LIFE PERMANENTLY.
THE WOMAN WITH THE ISSUE OF BLOOD, HER
MATTER CHANGED IN A DAY. 12 of
suffering, 1 day, that was it.
The Lord can bring you for 4 days
and give you a business IDEA
THAT WILL CHANGE whatever you are doing
and that will become your secret.
We are not just gathering for the sake
of gathering. This is our conference.
This is the meeting God has allowed us
to have. So, there is a demand for SONS
AND DAUGHTERS
PLEASE, TELL THAT NEIGHBOR, "NEIGHBOR,
HE'S HERE WHEN YOU WAIT."
HE'S HERE WHEN YOU WAIT.
HALLELUJAH.
TELL THAT NEIGHBOR, "HAKUNA KITU URGENT
KAMA HII."
AND YOU PLAN YOUR WEEK OUT MONDAY,
TUESDAY, WEDNESDAY, maliza kazi.
Thursday,
MAYBE NIKKI
UH
UTAKUWA UNAKUJA KWA OFFICE UNANIAMBIA
PASTOR NIKUOMBEA NAKULIZA ULIKUWA
DOCUSER.
SIKU ZOTE NNE. KAMA ULIKUWA NNE SAWA
NITAKUOMBEA. Lakini hapa sasa nilikuja
unajua mdozi. Huyo mdozi mwambie SIKU
ZANGU ZA LEAVE NDIO HIZI. Ine naenda NA
SO, KUJA UTUINGIZE KITU.
TELL YOUR NEIGHBOR, "WE MUST be
serious."
UH UH TELL THAT NEIGHBOR, "NEIGHBOR,
WE MUST BE SERIOUS."
TELL HIM HAKUNA ile I do.
Hii ni yetu.
Are we together?
[Music]
You know, I was surprised.
Some of the preachers,
God had to tell them to cancel meetings
to come.
So, what is the Lord planning for us?
What is it that the Lord has ordained
for us?
And this is not my meeting. Even me, I'm
coming expectant.
I also need There are things in my life.
Mganga jigangi, I need God to come
through.
Kuna kuna vitu lazima hii Docuser lazima
Mungu ashow up.
Yeah.
Kuna vitu lazima zitendeke.
Hallelujah.
Watu watapona. Pastor Kemadi ako hapa.
Huyu muujiza ni zake.
Na Pastor Morris.
Baba mababa ni wawili hapa. In fact,
watatu.
Apostle Juma, Bishop JB na Prophet
Maniki.
Na vijana watabarikiwa.
Tuko hapo mimi na Pastor George.
Hiyo ndio kizazi yetu. So, no one is
being left behind. And bring your
friends.
Bring your friends.
So, from this meeting,
there will be revelations
and authorizations.
Now, ukiingia maombi tuambie ndio
tukufunike.
Are we together?
Don't go blindly. Whatever Some of you,
the Lord will tell you go back to the
village.
The day you learn, he will begin to open
your eyes. You will sit with your mother
and she will begin to give you stories.
In those stories, you will hear things
and you will be like, "This is what I
was looking for. This is the
revelation."
Some of your aunties will begin to tell
you things
and you will I wonder.
Lakini
kitambo
hakuanga straight sana. Then unajiambia,
"Mhm, now I understand.
I didn't know, but now I understand. May
that be your portion."
I say may that be your portion.
Do you have the element of bread?
And And some of some people God will
tell them to go and break bread in their
homes.
Yeah.
There's a time one of my pastors,
every time we land at home,
some relatives, majority were
I told him, "Every And
he told me the day they broke bread,
none of them came. They had peace.
But there is something about it.
Sometimes you go and break bread just
declare in that home,
today, the blood of Jesus will speak in
this house." You You know the operation
you are doing.
By breaking this bread, any other blood
that has been speaking is nullified.
It's nullified.
And there will be victory.
There will be victory. One of the things
that families carries when deliverance
happens is wealth.
So, when the Lord wants to steal the
wealth, I mean the devil wants to steal,
he first of all attacks a family because
families are the institutions that God
has ordained for wealth.
The second thing we are going to see is
salvation of our people.
Some of you you you are the only one
born again. God will begin to add to
your number. Your brother will get born
again. Your sister will get born again.
And then you will discover there is a
formidable formidable formidable force.
And let me give the final instruction.
Some of you, the Lord will also anoint
you
to begin to do some things.
I remember where I come from, nobody had
ever gone out of Kenya.
The The day we attempted to go out of
Kenya,
we went to Masai Mara.
And it was a
It was It was a bus ya serikali.
And then we saw a stone.
And then we were told, "Huku ni Kenya.
Huku ni Tanzania."
So, we crossed and we said we were in
Tanzania.
And And that is the
I can't LIE TO YOU. TANZANIA WAS LOOKING
LIKE KENYA.
It that border I So, WE WE CONSULTED
OURSELVES AT LEAST IN MY END OF KENYA
and Tanzania.
But we had not crossed anywhere.
I remember one of my aunties
came.
And I was going I think I was going to
Britain.
And she came with a seed.
And she said, "I want to release this
seed because I've seen the Lord
is helping you to open the nations for
us." Today, she's the only auntie who
works in Britain.
Because she understood that this could
be my niece. She's my aunt, senior than
me.
But she understood by spiritual
protocols,
we have seen there's something God is
doing with this our son.
And she came and honored me.
Some of you God is about to use you as a
hammer.
If you Can I say something and I'm
saying it with a lot of love?
Yes?
Some of you it's not that you need a big
house,
but you will need to build a big house
to open dimensions in the spirit so that
generations will never suffer what
others suffered.
So, we are not just praying, we are also
becoming
pioneers,
breakers of ceilings and barriers. And
it is going to happen.
Pastor, how do you know?
Because
every pastor carries a certain grace.
And people don't come to a pastor, they
come to a grace. Because the grace the
man carries is for them. So, I know that
the people who come are people that God
is going to use as a hammers
to break possibilities.
Do you have the elements of bread?
Pray in the Holy Ghost for 1 minute.
Shh.
[Music]
IN THE NAME OF JESUS.
FATHER,
WE HAVE NO OTHER ALTAR TO RAISE.
WE HAVE NO OTHER SACRIFICE TO RAISE.
WE HAVE NO OTHER PRIESTHOOD ORDER TO
FOLLOW.
AND DEAR LORD, by partaking of these
elements,
IT IS A REMINDER OF THE EVERLASTING
COVENANT THAT WE are in.
AS WE ARE PARTAKING OF THE BREAD,
WE DECLARE
anything broken
because OF THE ALTARS IN OUR FATHER'S
HOUSE, wholeness is coming now.
ANYTHING THAT WAS BROKEN,
ATTACKED AND DESTROYED BY THIS BREAD,
WHOLENESS IS COMING.
LORD,
WE HAVE NO OTHER BLOOD WE CAN SHED,
BUT WE KNOW YOU SHED THE BLOOD ON OUR
BEHALF.
BY THIS CUP AND BY THIS BLOOD, WE
declare
let the victory that comes by it,
let it become our portion.
Any other blood shed in your lineage, we
command it to be silent from now.
And we declare
let the blood of Yeshua
perpetually speak IN YOUR HOME
AND IN YOUR FATHER'S HOUSE
IN THE MIGHTY NAME OF JESUS. WE partake
of this bread
and this blood with the revelation
of the reality of the new covenant.
And we nullify any other covenant made
in our father's house. You can now
partake of it.
Thank you, Holy Ghost.
Thank you, Jesus.
As the blood gets in your system, let
every disease die.
Let every infirmity,
anything that has another life, let it
perish.
Let the life that is in the blood become
your life.
Receive revival and rejuvenation
for them that are weak and weary, for
them that are tired, LET THE LIFE OF THE
blood begin to give you vitality and the
vibration of DESTINY IN THE MIGHTY name
of Jesus.
And let that blood speak over your life.
Let me receive the worshipers for 1
minute.
I just want us to sing one one song even
as we prepare to give
and as we prepare to receive the
announcements.
So, God